From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight.
Truth's get told, it goes unfold, we stir the soul with a tea surf cold.
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like the Awake has stepped in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like the Awake has don't look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
hello guys let's clear the air a little bit
now i don't know how big of a fan few times is on my show he's
i mean i'm just being accused of all these things on other channels that are not true like i have never
put my um i've actually done one members only live which you're allowed to do members only lives
but i've never like said
Maybe I think maybe I won occasion a few months ago
I may have you know tried out something or it's like I said, okay
Well today only members and mods or donators on which on the panel
But it wasn't a regular thing and it's like you acting like that's the rule and
Listen word misunderstanding
No, but uh
I don't know how long I'll be. You know I've been very tired lately not feeling so perfect, but I thought I'd come for a couple hours
Oh, I did try to go to betas and like you know be friendly and stuff
everyone's just like
Was like, you know the chair chat is kind of on my side a little bit, but
She's I don't know why she's doing so mean
But maybe we'll work it out, you know, I don't like to yeah
I know good times is like just he doesn't even come here. Like how does he even know like a
Even if I did have that system, that's my system to have it's like I don't go over people's channels
Tell them how to run their channel or anything like that. It's just so so funny how it's like I'm
Everyone's just like allowed to say I'm
Big so horrible and stuff and
Right
But I'm not playing a victim or anything like that, you know, I'm a big boy, you know, I can like handle
handle it
She stood up they just noticed the guys I didn't go where they're starting trouble. I started their new family and stuff
Hey, time. How are you? I?
Trying to be friendly and I get attacked and I just don't feel like sitting there just being
Called like the basic garbage in the world, right? Thank you, Samantha
I come here, I just try to have a good time.
I try to maybe make a little extra
so I can continue to do this full time.
I did already, you know,
I'm keeping the panel open tonight
because I had a nice donation earlier.
And so, you know, I'll use that to sponsor an open panel.
I mean, you know, I just want to make sure
I'm able to like continue and like survive
and stuff like that.
Hopefully you guys are having a good night. I'm not mad at anybody. It's like, you know, I
Oh, I don't try to
Whoo for myself
Not trying to like fucking stuff on anybody's toes or anything, you know, I'm just trying to
Have my own do my own thing
You're making jokes about the biscuit. I mean, that's fine. I mean it I don't even care, but it's like that I
Just set that up. So it's like it would just be a troll of me
Something that didn't really bother me as a troll just to see who we'd use it and like some people don't jump all over it
I love limp biscuit. It's one of my favorite bands, you know
So anyway, I finished my coffee I still got another little bit left I just burned myself with a
Brickett thing I can't find my headphones either. I can't find my headphones. I don't know where they are
Kind of frustrating
Because they're kind of big kind of big things to lose right, but I have my own my other ones in the
my
Hopefully I didn't throw them in the laundry. We're doing laundry today guys
Hey, Rudy. Hey, there's Rudy. Hey guys. Good to see you guys
Thank you, Samantha. I will just keep doing me, you know, it's like my show is doing fine
It's like I guess my success will be my best revenge, right?
My success will be my best revenge
And I am successful
And so, you know, I don't have anything negative to say about anybody though
You know, I hope everybody does well. I want everybody to succeed on this platform
not
trying to
again
Bother anybody or step on any toes
There we go lights on
Ooh
Hi guys, yeah, the norwish just inside here. Here's Rudy. Hi, rude. I say hi Rudy. Here's Rudy
Sweet cat
Good kitty cat
Yeah, so I've been doing some cleaning today. I did like four loads of laundry
Um, vacuums, I'm getting my, I got my bedroom in order a little bit.
Um, just trying to get everything good and stuff, but yeah, I love Vita.
Maybe she's just in a bad mood or something like that.
I don't, I don't need to like hurt her feelings, defend her or anybody really.
I'm just trying to, trying to live my life in my show.
Have fun.
Hopefully everyone's having fun. So that's what it's about. Not about hurting anybody's feelings or anything.
Okay
Grab my, I got a couple drinks tonight and
some cigars. I got these backwoods. Now it's like, you know, I was paying $1.50 for two cigars.
Now I'm paying $2.50 for one. Yeah, that's Mr. Rudy right here. Hey Rudy.
Oops, hold on.
Mr. Root. Hey, Mr. Root boy.
He's a cutie, huh?
My cutie Rootie.
Yeah, I love these cats and they keep me going. So whatever happens with any human beings, I
Got my kitty cats here.
I need to find a rival biscuits on to call it the troll beat it back. I don't know
What is it? It's a Persian biscuit. Look at my like a Persian biscuit
I'll keep bringing it up out of nowhere for no reason like hey, it's just a Persian biscuit song. What what what?
Just I'm just playing a nice song. It's just a Persian biscuit, right?
I'm just kidding. Hey J dog. How are you guys?
So I used to burn myself a little bit. I don't see my my frickin my headphones. That's really weird
Oh, I don't know you're right. It's like like what I
Don't want I don't want to troll though. I like I love I don't like to troll my friends like I
Understand why we have to fight right now
Yeah, but I don't know if there's a Persian biscuit song or what but maybe we'll find it
So these are pretty disgusting cigars
These are like backwards it looks like I was made in the back woods of like look at this look at this crap
So I have a smoke today. I
Will get my I will have to fix my camera, you know, I'm in I'm in this like you know
It's like kind of I have to look down at it right now, but how do I look? I look pretty good
Feeling pretty good tonight. Let's see. Let me put these headphones off
Yeah, it's just like my equilibrium is off a little because my ears clog like it's one ears clog
I'm gonna have to try to like
Get it out in the bath
But it's a little bit clogged. I'm gonna find my headphones. I don't know what happened to those
I hear something clanking around in the washing machine.
I'm getting kind of concerned that I accidentally
put them in the washing machine,
but hopefully that did not happen.
Hi guys, hey J-Dog, hey J-Base,
Cowboy's time, deviless.
Yeah, so just know that whatever good times I was saying,
he doesn't understand my show.
He's not even, I think he's come onto my show a few times
and just like, you know, he insulted me,
which is not really, it's like,
why would I go onto somebody's show
and just start insulting them?
No.
I would polite and say, hey, you're a fellow content creator.
Let's work on something together.
Let's collaborate and let's friendly.
I don't know.
Everyone wants to get mad at me, right?
OK.
So anyway, here I go.
But I can't wait to show you.
I will show you guys.
When I get my laundry done, I'll show you my other rooms
in this house.
It'll be pretty cool.
I just don't see.
My headphones tonight, so, you know, I don't know.
I'm gonna keep looking for them.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
What could I have done with them guys?
What could I have done with my headphones?
I don't know.
They're not in my bedroom.
I'm concerned what I did with them.
Okay.
Well, let's just hope they didn't go in the washing machine. That'd just be the end of it, but
Okay, here I come
Hey, we're how we guys doing
You once have to ear your drumming it was so dizzy. Yeah, that's how mine is kind of feeling right now
it's kind of feeling like
Kind of feeling kind of blocked up a little bit and uncomfortable and
It takes off my equilibrium a little bit
But anyway, I've got a third drink in this ice mash, hopefully these couple of drinks
will hit me good.
I'll take a rival biscuit song to bridge the gap.
I don't know.
I mean, how about a happy, you know, the KFC theme song, what's a finger licking good
or something like that?
I don't know.
What can I do guys?
Can you help me mend fences?
So anyway, we had daddy big miss on yesterday. He is a really cool guy. Hey look at wildcard Wednesday
Save to watch later. I'm gonna put my link up. So you guys
Feel free to come up tonight. No charge, you know, no no sponsor needed because we did have a sponsor
I don't know if they want to be mentioned but they did sponsor and so I'm gonna throw throw in a panel for them because
There's like an awesome person
Also
I want to say Christine was saying she didn't want to come to my chat again
Can you guys let Christine know that I will if she wants someone blocked and I saw who they want blocked
I will block those that person for them, you know because
Where Christine does a lot more appreciated than what the other person has done for me, so like you don't need to prove it yourself
You have a successful channel and business. So what do you keep doing? It's yeah, it's it is it is
But it's like, you know, I've made money this month and then a bit business like with all the slander and everything
It's like is it people gonna want to continue donating if they they hear all this crap about me and
You know, like I'm just like the worst person in the world. I'm doing all these bad things not doing anything bad
I'm just trying to do my show. Thank you time
Yeah, I can do a biscuit song Persian biscuit song. Yeah, I'll do a AI Persian biscuit song about beta and then
We'll see if she likes it
No, I think I think she would I think you would okay. Thank you time. Thank you dog
I want to continue to be, have a, you know, members.
I want to continue to have active panelists.
I want to continue to have people kickoff people at the panel.
I want to continue to sponsor panels.
I like all these ideas.
Some of the ideas are adapted from other shows.
Some are my own.
If it works for me, maybe it will work for you.
You know?
Okay.
Hopefully she'll laugh at it, you know?
I don't want to hurt anybody's feelings, you know, I love uh, and I love Vita
Hope uh, I think we're cool. I am a mod on her channel. So it's like it obviously she's like not that bad. Hey, what's up, rude?
Give me some in some please ease off. Yeah
Rudy's very soft cat though. He's a very soft cat
I do not like these fleas so
How are we guys doing tonight?
It's okay. It's okay. I don't feel it. I don't feel like that attack. I feel like you know misunderstood a little bit
And then whatever I try to defend myself. It's like, you know, there's so many people against me that it's like
I don't feel like it's really a fair fight
But yeah, you don't have to you don't have to apologize for her
Whatever whatever people think about me fine, so
Mmm
Okay, yeah, it seems like every few days we like make up so I think we'll be okay
Whoo, so I have a ham and cheese baguette I've been cleaning up my place a lot so
Then got a couple of drinks
Just hanging out with you guys
Let me see
Breakup or makeup. I know but I don't feel like breaking. I mean, it's like I don't have anything against her
I don't still understand like she gets mad at me
Every few days, it's okay
So
Yeah, and also like about like last night like I came on at like 11 30
I just woke up. I forgot that Spunky was starting her show like at 10 30
So I was already like an hour late
Then I got kind of caught up in a conversation with SD Monstro
and so I just you know sent people over to Spunky's chat and
That's regards from my chat and stuff like that and I'll catch her chat as soon as I can it's just like I already started and
I had only been on for a little bit and I wasn't planning on being up for very much longer. So
Okay, well, hopefully everything's okay. Hopefully everything's okay. Let's just
Give everyone a little break and I'm not mad at her at all
If I'm the easy target, let me just be the easy target.
I'd rather be than somebody else, right?
Okay.
Yeah, so it might be a shorter night tonight.
I'm not feeling 100% this week, you guys know.
Here's a couple of books I got, a couple of books.
So, good to see you guys, thanks for coming in.
We'll hang out for a little bit if you don't want to come on panel and say hi. It's not then
you know
You can always come on later
But hopefully everything's good with you guys
my
What's up big rod? What's up buttercup nut nut nut?
How are you big rod? I don't think I've seen you before welcome to my show
Everybody welcome to make last thoughts I can see
I got a lot of people on TikTok, too.
I've been trying to send over here and say hi.
If you have some TikTok shout out in the chat,
good to see you.
Welcome to the show.
Hopefully, there we go.
Time, I think you got a fan in the chat.
part of me guys that was really that was uncalled for I'm so sorry okay so I
yeah also I made some money today just by cleaning out my under my couch and
you see there's at least 50 cents and a kind of $2 and I can't pocket there we
So guys, I didn't tell you I got accepted to the Amazon
influencer program and I would
Let you know like Amazon does have an influencer program where you can like
make a little videos and stuff about your favorite products and and maybe like the
You know an influencer and showing people what you buy and maybe they'll
You know fluency by it too. And so you can check out
Amazon influencer program and apply for that
I was accepted, so I think if you have a decent amount of people on your channel and subscribers, you can probably be accepted in that, too.
Maybe have another monetization thing. It's better to have a lot of flows of monetization, you know?
The more the better, the easier they are, the better.
I've been also working with ChatGPT a lot. I really recommend you guys talk to ChatGPT about...
Your business or your ideas you can ask it. What are 10?
You know low-cost businesses to start like these businesses you can name some other business
You've done it will give you kind of in the genre of the area that what you're looking for
Maybe easy startups and then we'll walk you through it step by step of how to get it started. It's really amazing
So I recommend taking you out to chat since it's a tea for that
Hi, babe. Hi. Oh
Rudy's happy tonight
So anyway, how's everyone doing shout out to everybody in the chat tonight?
Look up you like my
The colors and stuff pretty cool
That was actually one of my first purchases on team and I was like wow that works pretty good
of course, I can't stop it from changing colors all the time now, but
Pretty cool still
Go through all the different colors
Hopefully it's not too psychedelic for you
epilepsy warning right okay okay I'm gonna write the biscuit song and so here
guys I'll just put this video on just real quick and I'll be right back in
like three minutes I'm gonna write the biscuit song I'll try to produce it
and everything I'll just put it on this video just real quick this will take
three minutes okay I'll be right back
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up the scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Scythe twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame. This ain't your mama's podcast. This a runaway train
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight boot flashing on cam chat losing their minds Mike
getting gong. Alex taking flight. It's wild, it's wrong, and we do it every night.
Paige got him simping, heart's in the chat, but she ain't got time for a dude like that.
Diamond flirting hard, let the girls react. It's a freak show party, no filter, all facts. Yo.
Yo Michael drops a line gong not tonight Alex try to joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways
Someone's got a fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says with a wink. That's the whole show sides half asleep. I still cracking jokes slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow
No rules just rolls. We pretend to play
And we're trending in the press welcome to the madness buckle up tight
Hey, back. Hey, guys, guess what? We have the premiere of the Persian biscuit song. It's gonna come out in a couple minutes
The AI is just finishing putting some finishing touches on it. I had it written and almost completed
So you guys are gonna be in for a treat here. We have the Persian biscuit song
It looks like it's just uh, oh here we go. It's almost done
Um, it's gonna be done in an air. Hold on
I think you guys will enjoy it.
Hopefully it'll be funny and, you know,
not offensive or anything.
I just want it to be a good, a good fun.
Hi, Bush Boogie.
Hi, Spunky, how are you?
Okay, is it almost done?
Okay, it's still in the process,
but it is a pretty fast, fast program.
So it should be done in just a few minutes.
Pretty exciting.
This is my sweet revenge, but it's all in good fun, guys.
It's all in good fun.
Oh, I love pizza.
Okay, so, let me just test it one second.
Okay, guys, I'm gonna try, this is a gamble.
This is a gamble, let me try it.
Okay, I'm gonna sit down.
Sleep this one, music, add music, okay, drive, save from Chrome.
Let's see what it's going to do.
Save from Chrome.
Hold on.
I'm trying to keep the chair in the chair.
Come on.
Hold on, guys.
Okay, it says download complete.
Hold on.
Okay, resets.
Come on, shared.
Downloads, come on.
It might be on the wrong drive over there, but let me see.
Five.
All right, I found it.
I found it.
OK, here we go, guys.
Here's the Persian distance.
with a tray and a smirk talking about biscuits like she did the work but baby
those scones are drier than Tehran where's the honey sauce girl it's gone
you say you're the queen of the big off crew but your butter slipped out like it's
dodging you I've got saffron cardamom rosewater drizzle you brought
confusion and a half big
Oh, here. Not over. Oh, shit.
I mean, it's not terrible.
Well, Big Rod, you kind of suck.
Someone, someone, uh, kind of, Big Rod. Big Rod.
Just so negative. I mean it.
Okay, thank you so much, Shady.
There's actually another version. I'm gonna try the other version
It sucked okay type him out please
And maybe that wasn't the best version
Yeah, we're trying this one now. Let's see if this is better. It's another version you might like this better
It's taking a long time to process.
Maybe that's good.
That's pretty good, but you need a little memory.
Yeah, I know.
Well, it gives you a couple of options,
but this one's just taking forever.
Good process.
Oh, here, it's ready.
Okay, let's try this one.
["Persian Funk"]
Persian funk meets penny poetic justice.
Bita came through with a tray and a smirk talking about biscuits like she did the work
But baby those scones were drier than Tehran. Where's the honey sauce girl? It's gone
You say you're the queen of the bake-off crew, but your butter slipped out like it's dodging you
I brought saffron cardamom rose water drizzle you brought confusion and a half baked fizzle. I'm the biscuit of
Under desert lights my biscuits got hips my biscuit
Yeah, I think I like that one better
Do you think we have a winner guys? I didn't know it's a winner. What do you think?
What's up, Evil Rod McDonald
It's only a beat in here you hear the song
Hi guys, I don't know what's wrong with everybody tonight. They're not you guys
All right, be here.
Thank you for timing up, people.
It was pretty good?
I like that better, yeah.
It was pretty good.
To do it in 10 minutes, or less than 10 minutes,
get a pretty good song out of it.
I think I'm doing pretty well.
Yeah, I knew a lot about Persian culture that I didn't know.
And I also said B to Jew, and that's what people call her.
I don't know what that means, but B to Jew.
Hi everybody
Here and people are coming in so the link is pinned
And look it's like two out in here or something. I'm gonna drink a couple couple drinks and maybe go to bed early
I don't know
Seems like it's gonna be another one of those quiet nights
But you know I like the
If people that talk shit about AI, it's like, I think should be the end, because AI in conjunction
with human intelligence, like you put the two together, you don't just let the AI go wild
and just do whatever it wants, you direct it, and it can be awesome.
I don't think people understand that.
Yeah, I give way too many of my secrets, too, but it's like I have a whole band in here
That was pretty good.
Hey, Ruth.
Hi.
So how are we doing tonight?
We have cards or something?
Let me see.
Where's my...
Let me check out what it is.
What is this?
A gesture?
These are good.
Hi, guys.
Give me a good shuffle.
Guys, check out my TikTok, by the way.
I do like, you know, my kind of fast readings on there,
but it actually really works there.
Like people actually just like all want readings there.
And that's pretty much all they want.
They don't want like any bit of bullshit.
And so, you know, it's kind of like different
from this show a little bit than that.
It's like, you know, focus on the readings
and stuff like that.
But, you know, this is my YouTube baby.
I thought we'll see how it goes.
I do get some kind of explanations there, too.
I have a membership there, too, already.
Monetized within three days.
New record, huh, guys?
Just the animal.
Where we got for the chat.
Just collected for the chat.
These are really cool.
Oh, look what popped out.
Okay, so we got the four of pentacles.
Okay, four of pentacles.
I'd say coming together
Maybe two couples or something coming together with an idea that could make a lot of money
I don't know if you're you're in a couple and then you know a couple
The four could be the magic number. Thank you Samantha
Okay, also war is like really like you got a you got a hold on the material world thing, right?
What else we got we got the sun. Oh all positive things the sun is all positive all good things the glorious fairy tale castle
The happily ever after the prince and the princess say that everything's good. Everything's bigger. Okay
That's what everyone is looking for
That's son, right? Okay. What else?
We got the Wheel of Fortune things are going in your favor or the Wheel of Fortune is going in your favor right now
I love the colors here, too beautiful like
green and pink
Yeah, Wheel of Fortune
Things are on your side. If you're on Wheel of Fortune, you'd be hitting the $10,000 $10,000 segment up the bank, right?
Okay, what else do you have the Emperor?
Maybe this is like a mature man. This is this one's kind of like Japanese
Yeah, this looks like a all the kings in the deck basically the Emperor
When he says goes he rules over the entire kingdom not just you know the Empire Empire not just the kingdoms, right?
There's maybe four kingdoms in the Empire
Use the head honcho, right? So I'm gonna charge through the meatless person. You are this person. What else?
Three of swords
Watch out. There's some heartbreak ahead. Maybe two, you know, you want to watch out
Don't get your hopes up too high certain situations and go with the flow and you will heal from any heartbreak, too
But that's not the best news. Let's get some advice for the chat
Two of swords is like maybe like, you know get out of like the tunnel vision
You're coming to a crossroads make the right choice cut what doesn't serve out of your life to your sword
They always think of it as a pair of scissors
Cut what doesn't serve you also like a television set though because
Like they're doing like this, right? Just taking the TV set. So thank you, Samantha. Well, that was the collective for the chat
You want to come on the panel? I don't know maybe
It's looking a little bit quiet these days I
Don't know. Why do I get so tired though? I get these I get these like shutters of
I think it's because I've been smoking this fake
The bait makes me sleepy, but I do have a couple beers. I'm gonna try to use a couple beers and
Hang out as long as I can
Wonder when beat is gonna get here
I read, yeah, I'm reading the energies of the chat, yeah.
And it does tire me out sometimes.
Sometimes it gives me energy,
sometimes it takes a little bit of energy, you know,
it does both, you know.
So maybe I'm a little bit extra sensitive to these.
I don't know, how's the moon right now?
We are in the Leo season,
so it does kind of burb right during the day.
Yeah.
I also had this protection soap I use and the soap really like, you know, it makes a difference, I think that's a really good soap, it's called Oliwe or something, Oliwe, Oliwe.
Smells really good.
So yeah, so my hair is getting pretty out of control, huh?
So I'm going to sit back with Rudy right here.
There's Rudy.
Hi guys.
We're more sage, yeah, I will in a little bit.
I'm almost out of my face too.
Do I look like, maybe I look like really dorky
and some people think I'm like really dorky,
but I'm really not.
It's like, I like, I like how glasses can like
change the perception of a person sometimes.
Hopefully it's not like all Jeffrey Dahmer thoughts, right?
But I like these a lot.
I like these glasses.
If you want to come up on the panel, I think I did pin the link.
By the way, they were talking about the paywall I do have.
I do have a paywall up because I get threatened so much with like, you know, flagging my videos
that I've just put behind the paywall.
After I do the show, the lives are all free, but after I do the show, I put them on members
I show nice and protected from the haters and stuff like that so
Members and there's a lot of members of over a hundred so they can see all the past episodes
Except the ones that are private and I have to go through those myself because some of those were probably form bombs
There's different stuff and so I'm gonna make sure I don't get any any trouble on YouTube. So
But how are we guys we're doing guys? I hope we're having a great day today. It was the 30th
So you have a few more days of a month
You want to have any questions or comments or
Ideas or all of our things I need to go over there because you that has had a few drinks
Okay, I will but say I want to play her the song and I can't play the song over there. I can just play it over here
There's a lot of weirds like you, but I love you Ilya and Ilya's porn bomb me, but it's like
We're cool though because there's a chance he had once time he had a chance to form on me
He did it. I fell asleep with him on the panel
And I don't know if it was divine intervention or something. Hey, what's up? Oh, Lola. Hey, Lola. Hey, Juan Lola
Okay over here. Hi
Hi Lola
Yeah, oh you're hissing at Rudy
Hi everybody, there's you right there. We're coming to you up. Yeah, so I don't see my headphones around. Yeah, let's miss Lola
Lola Lola likes to
Stay in the house a lot. Hi, babe
Yeah, Nora came in. Hey, there's tricks to your tricks is up there my tricks
Yeah, Lenore knows Lenore is just in you just root me. You don't do form bounds
Well remember when you took a pee in that in that yellow bucket and we saw your wiener
You want to pick purchase a show of Jamie's Cowboys at the farmers market. Yeah
Jamie get yourself on Amazon and stuff and then I'll I can promote it on my I'm not an Amazon
influencer
So I can promote products on Amazon. Oh
You don't sell stage Jamie. Jamie sells honey. I think she sells honey. Do you sell honey products too?
But Jamie's like a beekeeper
But maybe you should grow some sage because sage is a you know, wonderful wonderful crop
I think you probably can probably can make some dough from it too
The cats yeah make some honey
It'd be so cool to learn about honey and like to be in a little beaker outfit with like the smoker thing and like
Like watch the queen bee and like, I don't know
Drives like a slimy burger
You know hug him and Rudy. Yes, I give you a hug
Hi, it's from Jamie's cowboys
How are you?
Yep, you guys having fun come up on panel say hi to me
They got the panel open tonight. It's free panel open panel. We did have a beautiful sponsor earlier that
Timed out Canada Drive for the next 24 hours. And so hey rude. Oh, here comes Rudy
Hi, we're all coming up here. Say hi
You listen go hit them. Hi
You all get attention here they all come
Hi guys
Also my tiktok guys join my tiktok. It's fun. It's like quick readings, but wow, it's fun over there
There I think the taste though tiktok
And shit. Yeah, there we go. Let me just click on that link
I don't know if I get
Counts for inviting you guys
What's to sponsor tonight's panel?
It was an anonymous donor that timed out Canada dry and so if they want me to say their name
I will but I'm just sponsoring the panel in honor of them, but they're not anonymous as far as I know right now
Let's take step forward
It's a secret person
Timing out Canada dry
You have only YouTube and rumble. I don't know but tiktok is cool. I don't know. I think people like this
See, there's a really sexy people on tiktok. I would say they're
Or sexy and they're
Guys that likes it. Oh my god. It's fun. I
love Canada Drive ginger ale but
And I like the person Canada Drive but somebody has timed him out past three days in a
Persian funk meets penny poetic justice
Bita came through with a tray and a smirk
Talking about biscuits like she did the work, but baby those scones were drier than Tehran. Where's the honey sauce girl? It's gone
You say you're the queen of the bake-off crew but your butter slipped out like it's dodging you
I brought saffron, cardamom, rose, water, drizzle
You brought confusion and a half-baked fizzle
I'm the biscuit of Babylon lake
Okay, do you hear me now?
Can you hear me now? Not there's problems. I'd have to go on my other by this thing actually
Can you hear me?
Audio hello, do you hear me now? Oh, yeah, I think you do
Okay, good ten four
Okay, do we hear the song here you go if I can hear it
You tease with a tune about your beat to bite
But I serve mine warm under desert lights
My biscuits got hips, my biscuits got pride
Yours needs butter just to slide
I got Fok Levoi cousins and Toddy Groot
Your recipes lost in the back of my boots
Whip that dough like you're in a trance
But you'll never beat a Persian dance
Beat to June, this is not a biscuit
This is construction material
I think it booted off. Hold on. Let's see. Hold on one second. We have base stirfer. Hold on. Let's take it. I've heard of you. Hold on one second.
It's the same person. Let me just put my banner up. Hold on. Hello. Nager, Nager, Nager.
Well, I mean, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a
Justice
Bita came through with a tray and a smirk talking about biscuits like she did the work
But baby those scones were drier than Tehran. Where's the honey sauce girl? It's gone
You say you're the queen of the bake-off crew, but your butter slipped out like it's dodging you I brought saffron
Cardamom rose water drizzle you brought confusion and a half baked fizzle. I'm the best
under desert lights my biscuit's got hips my biscuit's got pride yours needs butter just a slide
i got baklava cousins and toddy roots your recipes a lot
oh hey what's up you like this song oh good yeah it was pretty good it's a new biscuit song i mean
it's like i think i think it's better than the other one i prefer baklava over the biscuit yeah
How are you God pretty good man? What's going on? Oh
Not too much. I found my headphones finally. I love these ones pooped out on me. So I'm just having a smash and
Hanging out. It was a little bit rough at beat us today. So what happened? Oh
You know, she had good times good times. Oh
So he doesn't allow anyone on the panel list. They pay their members and like it's like just untrue things and then she was like
Oh, thank you. Oh, I you know, I I said the white biscuit and then you go mad. Why?
It's like it's just like my you know, I couldn't take it anymore. I just
were just being mean to me on the panel and
So I just left but I don't think you mind one person being mean to you. It's when you get gangbanged up there
Yeah, and I was like five
Elda was nice to me, you know, I mean if it was gangbanging if they mean just use some Lou but at least I mean come on
They're so so rough. I mean, but uh, you know Elda was up there. He was nice and like clumsy
He was fine, but it's like, you know good times hates me and you know, Canada's not a fan. Yeah, I know
There is misrepresenting my show and like and then like you know saying oh
Money he's scamming people. He's like he's not good at tarot blah blah blah blah and it's just like why why so negative about me?
It's like everything everyone's to judge me about everything and I'm actually like out here doing it making some money on YouTube and like you know
And I'm not for you do it your way if it doesn't work you'll change it. That's it
Yeah, I'm this experience part of this experiment
So maybe I did do a day well
I said members only on the panel so what I'm allowed to do is my show so I can experiment experiment on it
Right, it's like you don't fucking like it pay the five fucking bucks and be a member for a month. What the fuck?
Fucking cheap pricks, man. Oh, it's the principal. I'm looking to pay. I should have to pay the good
Well, you're gonna have to fucking pay if you want this kind of super content. I don't care about the sunshine
need
Because mama
psyche I'm coming home
Oh, I love it. How are you doing? How are you doing, man? How are you doing? Sorry, God? Yeah, I'm fine
Try to smoke this backwards thing meet me and God he me and God he just played a three out of you know
Yeah, two out of three fucking chess game, dude
Checkers checkers checkers
And he fucking he fucking want my ass
We play we're guys we're guys we're just playing a Nokia and chess again. I mean come on. No
Checkers no, no, no, we played checkers and he almost had him, but then
V-chess, what is it called? It's like a million squares
No, no, no, like it was it was cool. No, yeah
Yeah, like Illuminati test you're playing it was kind of it was kind of weird and psyche psyche
It was kind of weird because like then like JT and fucking Vader was playing like against each other and then like
Vader was like a bad sport
Oh, and then he was like man. Why do you guys you guys get along you guys are great?
Even if you lose you guys are friends
I put myself in a mess. Where's everybody? Hey everybody. We're here with Goddy and and Ziggy. How are you guys?
How's your week been so far?
of this wacky Wednesday here like look at my at the wacky Wednesday
, sure we can do anything we want
, yeah anything goes tonight yeah it's wacky Wednesday, while I was like a second
all should all do that's cool made a U
Welcome to wild car wins. Yep. It looks familiar. Yeah
Thank you, we please do me one favor. I always ask you to do this and say what?
Go go like this go
Everybody
Remain quiet take your phones and put it on airplane mode while we ascend just do that
No, I'm not going to say that
Like a turd whistle in the heat
Guys if you find it better guys as soon as I get I'm gonna be able to buy a computer this month
Or as soon as my next payment or next month, you know if when my when my YouTube payment comes down, whatever
I'm gonna buy a computer and then I'm going to actually
Oh, you don't have a computer
I mean it doesn't really work very well and so I just haven't been able to use it for the show is very slow
And so I'm gonna get a new computer, and I'll be able to plug my microphone in there
I'm a professional studio microphone to use I have like it'll get a better headset. It'll all like it'll be better
How about a digital tarot program?
That you could put it on the computer screen on the screen here. Oh, I like it
Like it random pick of cards and stuff like that
Yeah, that'd be cool. I mean, it's like I also have some I have several tarot card
Programs to that I have on my tablet that I bought and they do very good readings, too
I mean, it's like, you know, it's kind of randomized. It has like some the detail of the deck
The description and stuff like yeah, because it warms it computer do the reading let it
Yeah, I can do yeah, I can I can do I can do both. Yeah, I can I can do both and
then I mean I'm into the new now some people are just very old-fashioned about
it like you know I guess shit for just even using AI so I think I'll just
continue to do like you know old-fashioned type readings but yeah oh my god yeah
don't ever use AI fuck that
And I have a new this is a new one that made of the of their the magician that
Laughing I'll make a ziggie car, but I have to get some more pictures of you
Who we have somebody some say that their name is respectfully so hold on one second
I think it's probably somebody we know hold on hold on what what's what which one?
Hold on
Okay
Hello, hey, what's up guys?
How you been are you back?
You know these guys. Yeah, she's a good friend. We go way back. Okay good good. Okay
Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh
I've been asking if you've been good
Oh yeah, I've been great
Taking care of business, you know
What kind of business are you taking care of?
How's Miguel been?
Life
I don't even know what Miguel
Oh, I thought you knew Miguel
My bad
Oh yeah, you might have the wrong person
Where are you, Florida?
No, I'm in Texas
That's why, yeah
Texas
I hear the crickets in the background why don't why don't you sound like a redneck like you're from Texas
Well, let me get this straight guys. No disrespect to anybody, but I'm just a regular human being you know
Well, yeah
This is how he does he get initiates people on to the panel like this
I will never engage in any type of friction. I don't want to be cruel with anybody. No, no, no, let's go cool here
We just we just test people to see if they can hold take the take the heat take the heat. Yeah, I mean
Exactly
But you have nine you have ninety five to a hundred degree heat over in Texas am I right?
That's where I'm at right now. I'm not really from Texas. That's where I'm at right now. I'm visiting
Where are you from?
Gary. Oh, Indiana. Yeah
Michael Jackson Dave Letterman
Fuck yeah
Do I eat pork? No. Yeah, why not?
Because it makes me sick. Oh, okay. Oh
She already knew why she doesn't eat pork. I know I don't want to say it
Why don't I eat pork? Am I you guys think I'm a Muslim or some shit? Uh-huh, maybe you could be
You said it I didn't say
Thank you Christian what type of Christian God, you know what type of Christian
There I really like as far as okay as far as religion go
There's really no title to it. Everybody put these you know stigmas with these titles and shit like that
But one thing about it. Um, I don't believe in God. I don't believe I know Jesus
No, I said I don't know it's not I don't believe in Jesus. I know him
You're not no, listen, you don't you might not believe in Jesus, but you're sitting right next to God
But do you know no wait, but do you know that God is real
Um God is Jesus is God. Okay, and that that is who God he is. He's God
Right, right. Nobody's god. No
Psych please
Oh my gosh, who cares. It's okay. No, no God. He
Psych God with a little G that with a small G
psyche like she she doesn't believe she she believes in Jesus but she doesn't
believe in God that's what you said when I say I don't believe in Jesus that
simply means I don't believe I don't use the word believe because within
belief there's no be a IE
You're being obnoxious, Ziggy being obnoxious, okay, hold on. I just want to ask, God, God, God, come on. Hey, Yumi, how are you?
Oh good good good. Yeah. Hi guys. Okay, Ziggy calm down. Stop laughing like a chimp
What do you mean an alien chimp? I'm was laughing at what she was saying. You're so loud. You're so loud
Turn me down. You're the panel. I'm doing I'm doing it
You know somebody said in the comments that I sound 16. I'm actually 30 30. I'll be 31 in August
Oh, you miss 32. Oh, dude psyche has tattoos. I never saw that. You have tattoos. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Was it your first time here?
Who me no, you know, you know me. He's talking to me. I didn't know it's like he had tattoos, bro
No, I didn't
Can I call you something else because your name is kind of long for me. Yeah
Long as it's not disrespectful. No, no, just give me something. I'll call you whatever you want me to call you other than that name
He's called me respectfully, respectfully copacetic.
Three syllables, three syllables.
I need something with two syllables at least.
Isn't that a song?
No, wait, wait, wait.
That's like an old 80s song.
That's three syllables too.
Respect, believe.
I'll call you RC, RC.
That's good, RC.
Okay.
Yeah, somebody in comments said I'm 15.
I'm not no fucking 15-year-old.
You sound like a 15-year-old though.
That's what they're saying.
No, he's not 15.
No, I know but she sounds like it. That's what they do me. She doesn't even fork you to you me
What do you think of that? I have a very light voice. I can't help it. So
Yo, you haven't really talked she sounds like a five-year-old
It's it comes from my grandmother my grandmother has a very light voice like myself
Is it like a syndrome or something? No, it's not a syndrome
Oh, okay. No, no, some people have that. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I'm 4'11", but I'm not 4'11".
Oh, there it is, there it is.
I'm not 4'11", or anything, but when I was younger, I used to be very self-conscious about my height, you know.
Well, I mean
So you should be really self-conscious now
You don't wait like 400 pounds do you like cuz when I when I was a kid I was like, you know, I was like what fucking like five
four
Middle school and then fucking like I was like so
Now and then now I'm six foot two. You know what I mean, so
That's okay, nobody's complaining about your height. Oh, yeah
Actually, my little niece is actually taller than you actually if you're wait, we're worried about we're worried about how big you are
I'm so, I couldn't bust a grape in a fucking fruit fight. Like I'm small as fuck.
Oh, jeez. Oh, so you're, so wait, wait, wait. So you're not like, like when you get in a fight with a woman, let's say, or a man, whatever you do.
No, no, no, but, but let me ask you this.
Okay.
And you're that short and you have that high pitched voice. You're like basically
On it, you're right. I'll fuck you up. I'll beat your ass
Got it. I see what she's doing. Yeah. Yeah, I'll fuck you up, dude. She will fuck you up
like no doubt about it
When that is fucking good shit, I like that shit
Why is you me so quiet?
When loser draw I will fuck you up. It's serious. She's like, well, no that one is like basically fuck Americans
I don't want to be here and then especially if there's a woman here
How do you feel about Hulk Hogan?
Yeah
God rest his soul.
Thank you.
That's it.
She's a good one, this girl.
I like her.
I like her, dude.
I like her already, too.
I do.
Yeah.
Do you remember that moment when he walks out with a cane
and fucking to rescue his boy from a DUI and shit?
Yeah, I remember, dude.
That was crazy.
What?
Are you guys talking about Hulk Hogan?
Yeah.
You said he you said he rescued a guy from what?
No, he came to his son whenever he got a DUI and he was like, did he do this?
Oh, he did. I mean, that's what a parent's job is, you know, to be here.
You me, you me, I'm sorry. You me, I'm sorry. That thing makes that thing makes you look fat today
If you could take that off, it'll be much better
Oh, she didn't know it you mean if you didn't wear glasses. We know it's not the glasses
Please I'll be nice if you take the glasses off, please. Why are y'all being mean? We're not being mean
I'm just gonna be mean I don't let her know sometimes
You guys ask me a question. Can I ask y'all a question, please? Yeah, go ahead
Okay, and I want to hear you guys. I want to hear you guys out as well. Um, do you guys believe in Jesus?
Yeah, he's real well, of course, okay
Why why?
What why would you ask that because it was asked to me and I love Jesus, you know
Like I said
God is that way now. You need to ask me. Do I love Jesus?
No, I don't I'll be 31 August 3rd
Third yeah, you got a birthday coming up RC
I guess you're an August baby, okay?
Whoa, Ziggy, sing Happy Birthday to her, go ahead.
No, no, no, no, don't do it, don't do it.
Happy Birthday to you, Happy Birthday to you,
Happy Birthday dear, don't know her name.
Happy, it's not your last year anyway.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
I'm in September. That's bad luck. Please don't see me. Happy birthday until my birthday. Okay. Okay. Okay come back then on the third
We'll be ready. Okay. Yeah, you like that cake and we'll do it in sync
Last year I got ice cream ice cream cake. I'm not really a cake fan
Yeah, yeah, I'm not at all. What about clowns you like clowns? No
We know a guy
Yeah, we do
The country
So my mom's my mom's sided family is from Tupwiler, Mississippi, right? Oh
Be mud I've had some Mississippi mud before who's got the TV on in the background
That's the dope. No, that's not me
It's like a radio play in the background
Is that you
No, I'm not playing shit. It's not you me. It ain't me. That ain't me either shit
It's probably where's that shit? It's only a little Iraqi friend. Oh here. I don't know radio. Oh
What a fuck is not oh shit. Oh shoot. It was you the whole time. It was you
I don't I don't know if you know this enough, but I'm a private investigator. It's my job to find things out
All right. Oh, yeah
Next time don't lie
Yeah, don't lie about it. I'm not a liar. We'll find out
You can't be a liar with us or that's the end
There's no second there's no second chances
Do you know Psyche?
Arcee, do you know Psyche?
I got a fart.
Psyche.
Huh?
She just said she got a fart.
What the fuck?
Who sent you here?
Somebody sent you here to fart on this channel?
No, no, no, no.
Are you one of those silent but deadly people?
No.
So the average human-
I see. I see. What's with the
music? What are you playing?
Oh, I'm just listening to
You were all hearing it. Huh?
We can all hear it. Yeah, stop
doing that. We don't mind if you
play it. It's just that psyche
doesn't like music on his
you know what's kind of weird?
And whatever I didn't hear her music, but I on on the discord dude. I couldn't hear your music. What the fuck? I
Don't know. I don't know how that works. That was weird. Yeah
That's a cutie that's a little cute. Who's that that wasn't you
That wasn't you, that's not you, that's not you, that goes too cute to be you.
That was me.
One second guys.
No, that wasn't you.
We don't have all day.
But first of all, she didn't have a fucking thing on her head.
So, that's not you.
I'm getting into I know I get that feeling now. I'm gonna be like, okay. Okay. Okay. All right
I wasn't I wasn't feeling that conversation
Yep, do it. Yep, you do it. Hey everybody in the lower chat wants us all to get off the power press one
Don't let Billy up here though. What happened? Oh my god, please. Don't let me up. What?
You she didn't like your voice
You scared her so she left
She left because you made that face. You scared the girl dude. Why do you make that face?
You had the thing on your head and you fucking didn't make up and
confused everybody
What's all that fucking noise? Holy shit? What's going on over there that's bombing? I
Don't even know where psyche is. Why does he never fucking come over
Thank you, are you mr. Yeah, she always did that to me, too. I hate it
This is a panel see
Look at look at look at your look at the chat it says good
Bita is in here psyche she's spying again. Bita. I hate you. I don't like
you. She's going to say taste the biscuit. Wait look. She said it already. Oh no. I hate
that fucking girl man. Why is she hopping so much with the biscuit? Bita just give her
the biscuit. Just give it over with.
Oh, Miss Liz, of course she likes me too, I'm sorry.
Persian dance.
Wow, she's just the biggest part of her culture.
Yeah, Parker.
If you're supposed to be crumpled.
There's another Persian beat.
Bita came through with a tray and a smirk talking about biscuits like she did the work
But baby those scones were drier than Tehran. Where's the honey sauce girl? It's gone
You say you're the queen of the bake-off crew, but your butter slipped out like it's dodging you
I brought saffron cardamom rose water drizzle. You brought confusion and a half baked fizzle. I'm the biscuit of
That's true
material.
well that was nice
my woman, she came at me with my woman
that was real nice
she's like Jan, I fucking, if you're gonna be with him
then I fucking, we're not gonna be friends
what a bitch
is this gonna kick off an AI song war?
cause I'm not here for it
Just thought that was shitty man. I didn't I never fucking you don't like a music
Yeah, I know you got a thing for a music. No, no, no, I'm saying no she said
Bita said they're fucking Jen and if you talk to Ziggy again, then we're not friends like what you little bitch
I knew you before fucking God and thank you. Why are you put this fucking?
There's the bitch right now. Hell. Yeah, I'm glad
Right now is psyche who picks like AI songs. I will battle rock you right now
I'll give you a whole fucking right now. What do you mean? Where are you psyche?
Oh, you can do it. Just like be a keyword warrior and make some stupid
Happen to you psyche, I'll be right back. I'm gonna roast the fuck out of you
I'm gonna do it in real life
All right, all right your wrinkle face pencil neck
You fake-ass scammer, you fake-ass scammer, you little fucking gypsy tarot card reader.
You have a bunch of my crickets and my cockroaches like Ziggy up here.
Keep flaking my breadcrumbs, these are my biscuit crumbs, Vicky is my biscuit crumb,
and everybody on your panel is my biscuit crumb, alright biscuit crumb, every single one on this
I got 50 people over there.
Little beada.
What's up AI boy?
All right, gay boy.
You don't listen to her, you know what I'm saying.
Siqi is a pussy.
He can just play a song, right?
No, because you hate men.
I'm going to tell you something.
Siqi.
You hate men.
That's what I just saw.
No.
She hates men.
I'm going to give you fucking five seconds to get up here.
She's a fucking awesome bitch.
I'm going to give you five.
For
All of them five don't do it. Don't do it three two
One do it. Oh, yes, I am
Your one hole is gonna be exposed. It is a lonely little bitch. That's all she is
Oh, she's made a nice card for you and everything. Why are you yelling at him poor guy?
She's a bitch man. I fucking hate that fucking thing. It's all about a biscuit. I don't know
I know I know I got a little problem with her because fucking dude
she's
Mouthing off at me dude. She
Knew me back in the day
Then I fucking have Jan and then she fucking just out of nowhere
She's like and chance by the way if you're with Ziggy then fucking I would never fucking talk to you again
Like motherfucker fuck you
I fuck that bitch man
You take that serious?
No, I do. Yeah, she's a mouthy little mother fucker.
What and?
What you what?
Mr. ZV, why are you so annoying?
Why are you wearing a fucking hat?
Everybody's on some shit tonight.
She's so annoying.
With your cloth hat dude, why why isn't everybody positive be positive like me?
You gotta have like a hat hat you don't have to fucking put the thing on come on
That's Persian that's fucking what she's used to that's what she grew up with
She's taken up for fucking
Beta because beta grew up in Persia. That's what they do back there though girl women shut the fuck up
Back then what do you mean back then?
Back there women shut up. They don't they can't wait now now now they do now they do
Before they did it
Exactly
What you say
Now it's too much. You just told you shut the fuck up. I know yeah, and not in that some
From the Middle East and fucking telling the fucking me
There's summer
No, no, no summer. So yeah, thank God to summer me and fucking go ahead you want to
You don't want you don't tell her summer we played fucking checkers
Over your ass and fucking he won. I he did he won
No, we were bad on it we were like dude
okay well he brought it up he was like okay over summer's ass and I was like dude
she's cool yeah okay over summer's that he beat me the first time and then I got
like serious and then I fucking won
The second time and then the third time I fucking made bad choices and he fucking won. So
Like fucking like like five kings and I wasn't doing well at all. Oh god
you know JT and Bader I know Bader okay so there's JT too
And then they they were playing like same games and shit and then fucking beta got asked her and then fucking
Mike
He came over to our game, and he's like, why do you guys laugh so hard core?
I thought that was funny. You drunk man. Oh, yeah
For sure
Yeah
And somehow I got stuck in between it, and my knee hit the ground, and my titty got caught, and one of the, I don't know what the fuck I did, I keep on, and my husband started fucking, you don't have to fucking do that, I was like, I don't fucking know, you didn't hear me fall, he's like, well, you're always fucking falling though.
Did you get a treat today too?
Yeah, you walked into a tree today, too. I think I walked in a tree and I almost had a
Grace
Hey, yeah summer listen, you're here now. Can you do some about that beta and psyche?
I mean, it sucks and I'd rather not get in between it because I love both of them and I just wish it would stop whatever's going on
I don't I don't I think beat is a fucking little bitch and that's just me
Everybody's loud
Right. Yeah, exactly. Oh, man, you summer dude. Did you watch fucking the office?
fucking
Yeah, I watched some clips of it. I was sleeping. That sucks man. There's a lot of people man. Yeah
Wife and as somebody that's married to her best friend my heart really broke for his wife today
You can tell she was struggling. I've seen a clip where they were laying their black roses on everything you just saw through.
Who is this? Oh, Yakuza. All right.
Come on.
Dude, I like white women. I don't like talking to you.
Well, she's been up here and she's not here for you to like her, Ziggy.
I mean, I don't know if you've got that news article yet, but she's been up here.
And we're not going to be mean to you unless we can see the difference.
And whatever.
And then you'll get me on your watch.
I don't work with girls like that, Dan.
I know, I know.
Whatever fucking report that team's going to keep fucking six feet under.
Oh
She might be involved it's not fast. Well, yeah, of course it's sad to you because you guys are Middle Eastern of course
We want it. We want it. Yeah, we're talking about that, but no one cares. Like, let me do that. But like, so what? She's been all used to her. She's got whatever she has to give us like that's not going to be the topic of the conversation. Yeah, I told her about you. She's down. She's totally down with it.
Mr. Ziggy.
Come on, save us. I mean, I'm saying, come on.
Oh, okay
She said oh, okay, dude. I forgot to fucking tell you
This girl was like me and I can't remember you're gonna have to remind me summer
But one of her friends was like, yeah summer fucking passed out
I don't drink I don't pass out I pass out to go to sleep, but I don't drink so
Whatever what what yeah, but what was it during though?
We would do like
She I want to I want to feed you me pork is what I want to do
I don't know what that is just a farmer just chicken farmer. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Here we go. Here we go. Oh, yeah
Sad I don't like business, you know, she'll do it
She's done it no do it do it actually put it
You know, you know what happens she gets very shy sometimes
Three exactly good. Sorry. It's one thing the people are doing shit, but no one's doing anything. I don't know what she's counting for
Okay, you'll be a coward you coward
About what?
You're a big oh my god, are you serious?
It's like how about this?
This is what's annoying. I want everyone to turn their camera off
How about that?
Don't try to attack the woman, especially from Middle East. I'm not attacking a woman. I'm
Middle-Easter
Okay, I'm a bully for the bullies. I'm not that with Billy. I want them to turn the camera off. I want it
I'm dedicated. I kind of can't show you my thing.
Miss beta was so kind to you mr. Zee. Oh fuck you
Here we go girls club
You know what? I like I like summer because she's not in a girls club. I like that
This is you
No, turn your camera off. Thank you. No, thanks. You'll be covered
You always be be covered. I have done it a million times. I don't want to do it
Online I've been on for about an hour or so
Okay
Yeah, this is not really much going on here. She fucking got like fucking cheese
My husband made me a steak and then I'm gonna eat that and I got my noodles. I like noodles. Oh nice. Oh, yeah, get some rest in there
We'll be here
Okay, I'll be back. Y'all have fun
All right, so
When's destiny Kevin on is she working tonight? Well, she's off because the channels been taken down. So
Oh, yeah, that's what we'll do when I go live we'll just send her the link and have her come over there
Exactly. Yeah, she wants to definitely
Okay, cool. All right. I'll have to be back a little bit later summer
Why, why did she do that? She went, bye!
What's that noise though? Are you still upset?
Who, me?
Yeah.
I'm still waiting for you to turn on. You can, Mr. Z.
What about me?
What about me? What about me? You don't want to see me? I saw you
I want to say this I want to say this to her
Misses you
I'm not gonna do it again because I'm dedicated to
Why oh why and what do you mean why I lie I don't lie and then fucking then that's the
tattoo shit this
And then fucking I'm just dedicated to one certain woman. That's all I don't need you. I don't want you. I do not care
You understand
No, I am not I am no because I do I have done visuals in fucking stage presence and everything
We're not
On stage and I want you to make up. I want you to make up right now
Get her tell her give her a hug
Siggi give her a hug. Okay. Can we have a virtual hug?
You me hug him out. I get up you Muslim hurry up. Come on. Come on. Hug it out you two
You must let me better hurry
Hug it out
Okay. Come on. Come on. Let's hug. Hug. I want to hug. Come on. Hurry up. Let's go. Hug. Hurry up. Come on. Are you done?
You mean you at work? Yes, I'm at work. Oh, we didn't know you were at work. Oh, she's in a call center. She's in a call center. She's at work, dude. Yeah, chill. Chill. You're gonna get a fired, man. You're gonna get fired, don't...
Don't say anything
You so annoying Mr. Ziggy. I never liked
Why because I'm not I'm not with your God is he an NPD
I don't believe in your God I'm at work. Oh, you said you're at work. Yeah
She's gonna show us a job. So you don't make fun of her. Oh, it's a colson there watch. Oh, come on, man
Don't don't make out. No, she did it. She's done him a poor dude. Yeah, sweet kid. Come on, man. Come on. Don't
Serious what what's poor girl?
Poor girl
Still wearing that shit, you know actually I should put Jan in that shit
Put a damn thing on her head and yeah on Jan
Yeah, no fucking way I'm like I'm like who works or into it remember she put on that witch costume
Is she is she a cam girl?
No, she's in a call center. That's what would happen in the Middle East man
Then no, there's so many people like to the left and the right of her right now. Yeah
Somebody's backstage
It's a surprise guest
Yeah, but that's what I'm saying
Right here what she's saying
What she's talking it's left in my yeah, good work
What's that a trapper keeper?
Plastic
Yep
This is my bad pay. Oh lunch. What's for lunch? Oh water. What's what kind of water? Oh
phone
What else she's she's the girl that fucking when you call a fucking company man
Is like a flying monkeys
It is. No, that's what you are like monkey. I actually I actually pictured you
Hello, can I help you?
Oh another flying monkey. I'm
no fighting. No fighting. No
fighting. My name. My name's
Veronica. I'm your dad. Yeah,
you're my YouTube dad.
y'all, y'all head y'all head
y'all head y'all head y'all head
Oh shit, Liz is ready to go
She just said you're flying dipshit
Probably
Let's go ahead write everything. I'll say it. I'll repeat everything you write
I've seen you before mr. Gotti two times. Did you like it? Did you like it?
What did you think one out of ten? What do you give me?
Clearly I'm not a call center. I'm not a call center. I guess she didn't hear me. My job is teaching. I don't even know what she said
She says she's not a call center. She's not a call center
You should have showed left to right and then yeah, she is
Turn your ugly cam off
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
It's a scam please. Sounds like a scam book. Yeah
Stupid Americans are there's stupid money, right? Yeah
I'm calling for a special offer on your warranty
Oh, you know what that said?
Do you know what that said?
I know exactly what that said.
That's the scam.
This is the scam manual for fucking what they have to do.
Well, what can you do if they ask for a manager?
Put them on hold for like 10 minutes.
Pretty much.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
All right, my name is Abou.
That those are the worst ones, but the these these
Promise the full refund of me
Middle Eastern's bother you mind if I put you on small hold. Thank you 20 hours later
Let me check with my manager thinking what's that
What was that a lawnmower that is a tool what kind of tool can't fool
Engineering
You know civil engineering
Well, then why are you in telemarketing then? What are you? What are you doing? I'm a secretary
for my boss. Oh
You're the secretary
You do a special activities
Don't be so stupid. Yeah. Come on, Ziggy dude. I mean I'm trying to get with it
Come on. I'm a dad bro. I'm a dad dude. I'm looking up. Come on, you know
I'm trying to get with it
You know, she really doesn't like you dude. Oh, no. Yeah, she hates it. You could tell
Well, I mean, I like she's the type of girl that I would like grab this towel and then like I would
Do you think he's a fucking asshole
That's funny. That's funny to me. She's playing American music
She's she's she's against me and then she's in where we're in that on her head
But yet she's listening to American music. That's where Jay pop kind of crazy
Yeah
You me
Stop playing fiction. You're not
You me you me I heart you I heart you I heart you you me I heart you you mean I want to I don't heart you
I heart you I heart all I heart you you've asked is to miss Peter. I don't agree with that
Why are you being racist? I remember how how she let you
In on a stream and then you've been racist and you're calling her as a person or whatever
What are you talking about?
You're done. It is the big baby. She's a giant baby. You're dumb, okay?
She's like, you know, but you've been racist to her. I never be racist. Don't be racist. Oh my god
She's like things cats are like beautiful
That's weird
Even if even in your culture, you don't even like cats. That's why
And you don't like dogs, you know that I know nope. I know what their culture is they do not like dogs
Straight up and they don't like cats who?
The Middle East they do not like that. They're eating the cats
Do bro when I was in a dog bro listen, I'm gonna I'm gonna listen. I'm gonna keep it short
When I was in Iraq, dude, there would be all these like dusty ass dogs like in the fucking foreground, you know
and
We're like what the fuck is
What's happening?
Dude these people don't like dogs or cats, you know what?
Right yeah, well here's my point. No what cats do
But they would fucking like our boys would fucking like grab a dog a wild dog and fucking like
You know make it domestic and it would do it and then they would ask
Hey, can I take this back home?
And it would work. Yeah
You know, there's an island in Japan that's full of rabbits
No
Yeah full of rabbit in fact it's so bad. There's two islands. There's two islands. There's one full of cats and there's one full of rabbits
Okay, yeah, it's a true story. Okay
Yeah, but my point is is that oh rather Middle Eastern's don't fucking they don't like cats
They don't like dogs look into my eye
straight up
Look into my eye
look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye
Look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye.
Look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye.
Look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye,
look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye, look into my eye,
I
Didn't fail you're under my spell
Yeah, I'm I'm I'm I'm seeing my you can't even talk. Yeah, you're under my spell
Later, she's up here man. She's wearing her little hooch
Thing man, that's funky. I see sponkeys down there. Wow
What are you doing all the way down there?
We're way up here.
Oh no, Spongebob is cool.
Fuck dude. I like Spongebob.
She's funny as shit.
Are you Mr. Ziggy?
Are you a simp?
Oh no.
Oh no, I have a woman.
I have a woman.
I don't have you.
No, no, no, no, wait.
What do you mean I'm a simp for summer?
Me and fucking
Fucking gaudy fucking plate checkers
And that was the game. That was it. I lost
He won and it was fun as
Are you stopping you stopping shipping your woman?
What do you sipping my woman? What are you talking about?
What does that mean?
Like you don't know you're women. Oh, yeah, I pimper out all the time. Yeah
Why not?
I'm not used to being a woman. Why why? Well, no, I pimper out for money. That's what I do
That's exactly what I do, but we
You know
Bader's in here man. He was against what?
Got he he was he was good JT, right? He got like real pissed
Me and howdy don't get pissed off that kind of shit
We think about that we think about that
There we go
Lucifer. There he is. There he is. What? God, if you're God, why are you Lucifer at the same time?
It's not Lucifer's eye. That's the all-seeing eye. Yeah, Lucifer. Okay.
I'm about to change it. Anyway, I'm about to change the
Why are you mad?
I'm not mad, but I was wondering why Lucifer was on the panel.
Oh my gosh, that's not Lucifer at all.
Not the red, the blazing red eye.
I just had a nice shower.
Yeah
Did you watch them bad hatred did you wash away all that hatred that you
Yep
He said he watched it psyche, did you actually watch it because she's a little bitch
I hate her man. All right, dude. All right. All right. You've told us like ten times you hate the woman
Yeah, well, no psyche's back. So I get to tell him that now
That's a nice shirt. You like that shirt, you me
You mean you me's not interested in a fucking thing that we do or talk about look at it
Jesus boy, we could be dead right now. She wouldn't give a fuck
No, Yumi is calling you right now.
Mr. Yumi.
Mr. Gotti.
Yes.
What?
Huh?
Can you see me from the side chat?
Yeah, I can see you.
Why?
What are you doing?
No, no, when you, when you, when you're on the side chat, can you see me when I...
No, I can only see you up here.
I can see you here.
Let me see you.
The private chat, the private chat.
Oh yeah, I can see you.
Yeah.
I can see you because I have a wrench.
Turn your ugly cam off.
Is that Paige?
Hey, Paige.
Hi.
Hi, Paige.
How you doing?
Hey, how are you?
Hi.
What's going on?
Oh my god, she doesn't have her cam on.
That's awesome.
OK, good.
All right, cool.
Are you talking to me, Ziggy?
No, I'd like you I'd I'd like when you don't have your cam on I think yeah, well, I like when you shut your fucking mouth sometimes
What about you you my like like you me or whatever
Well, no, shouldn't she like shut her camera? Hey, if you want me to get rid of him, I'll get rid of him in a second.
No, I'll do something to stay first, and then maybe.
Oh, she probably will. She'll probably have.
Why are you judging everybody? Why are you judging everybody all the time?
I am not. What do you mean?
You are one of the most judgmental, and you try to do it low-key.
Are you kidding me? I told you that you had the best hair.
Yeah, and then you told me you fucking needed something else about me.
Do she? I think so.
Looks good. Are you perfect?
Show the other side.
No.
Well, then maybe you shouldn't say those things.
Yeah, there you go. That side.
Yeah, look at that. That was good.
Look at that.
And I'm well that part right there looks like I wouldn't I gave a warmer to my dog
You mean it's okay camera angle it was just about camera
I just want you to be a nice a gentleman a man about I am I am a very good gentleman
Both of us
If psyche said that I'm an asshole, then I'm gonna be pissed. We said it. I did and we said it's the exact same time
With you, what do you mean?
What what I can't have an opinion
Uh, yeah, but you can't fucking tonight as I was I hear kidders. Oh, I found a kid. I rescued
I love that I'm gonna tour up and bleeding though. Yeah, I don't know. I don't know with you
Yeah, I saved them. They're right here. You heard me. I heard me. Alley. Can we see him? What did you save?
I saved some chickens. Because I'm not an asshole.
Chickens. Chickens.
Yeah, the Grinch had a bigger heart.
The Grinch had a bigger heart.
No, I gotta think that way, man.
Like, okay, let me ask Gotti.
Gotti knows me.
Do you think I'm a Grinch?
Ziggy, I don't give a fuck.
I just want to see these cats right now.
I mean, we're going on and on about you being a Grinch.
Ziggy, I actually do think that you're a nice guy
some fucking time, so it's not to me, okay?
that's all yeah okay so i'm going to find a flashlight so un momento señor oh they're on the
dog okay yeah she needs Spanish in the meantime we'll watch you meet me
Spanish no i don't know Spanish i just know that
What
You're like a mean version of big pipes
Yeah, you're flesh like
I have one of those boy let's fuck you guys together or separate
That I don't know if they're at the same house or in each other's houses
They're probably at the same place that I'm not gonna lie that sushi looks like shit
Where I don't even see
How are you doing? I was doing
What is it? Whoa, whoa, whoa, let me finish my statement. Thank you. I was doing good until I saw you me put that sushi in her mouth
Where is it you guys put all kinds of sushi in your mouth in your day, you know
We can do it on cam but I don't think Psyche would go for it.
Well even he had sushi in his mouth once he was in fond of it.
Just once.
She was 400 pounds.
Psyche.
What is that?
Is that a vagina?
Oh that's your finger.
He quickly took gas to that.
Okay.
Alright.
Can I pose something?
Hold on.
Where are these cats?
Oh here we go.
Oh, it's we're gonna have a hunt
No, I just I've been in the dark at my work. Hold on. Oh, yeah, it works though. Oh, no
I'm not I wasn't working today. I was golfing and I just worked and save my god. Where's your hair?
It's right here. Duh
Yeah, you shut the you shut up. Did you right now? Oh my god
Here we go
Well, it's like just a big handle like I gotta bring him to the SPC a tomorrow
You see what you're doing you're working are you are you working for government?
No, but I'm working for God, you know doing God's work. Thank you. You're doing God
You don't say anymore
She's doing fucking God's work right well these guys little guys. They were scared
They wanted you don't want to keep one watch you keep one because I already have four cats
And that's like way too many cats for one broad, you know, you would
Are you are you emotional?
Yeah, I mean they're cute shit
If I showed you a video of me shooting you guys sweet sweet dreams you too really
No, I don't really care if you shoot a raccoon. I mean like I don't have those here. I'm not really I'm not really fond of those. I don't care
Okay, we'll just kind of a rodent. It's kind of a rodent, isn't it? Yeah. Uh-huh. Yeah
Yeah
I mean I hunt and fish and I still eat that and you hunt you don't hunt
honey, please
She does, she has a moose head on her wall.
She really does?
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm native, that's how we, you know,
and we have another cattle farm too,
like we hunt and we kill stuff to eat.
Yes, we do.
Oh, she's a farmer chick.
Okay, now you're winning me over.
Okay.
That's what it's all about.
You know that page, winning them over.
You gotta win them over.
I wasn't trying to, but I'm glad I did.
I'm gonna give these babies
Let's auction them off. Let's let's auction the cats off a charity
Yeah, that's perfect fuck yeah, let's get charity of your choice
What is that like the skin of them?
I thought it was catskins
That's getting cats. Oh, she had skin cat
Don't lose them
I'm not going to lose them look at that butt look look at that butt. Oh, hey
I'm trying to do nice things and you're not nice
Me and nice right now. Okay. You see the babies one more time. Look at the babies hiding in the cozy knees
Look at how cute they are. They're so angry.
Ew.
They're so terrified of the light.
Burn that.
That one looks like a gremlin.
And then that one looks...
Oh, they're just so scary.
Ew.
It does look like a fucking gremlin.
That black and...
Yeah.
What the hell?
So you can't take them in the house for the night?
This is not...
I'm not at home.
I'm at my co-worker's camper that lives at my work in the campground.
Take it like a bottle of gasoline I mean squirt it in there
Are you wow?
You you probably should be you should probably be locked up
That's mentally unstable business
Wow, okay. Well, oh, oh why you miss eating too. I mean come on man
It didn't phase the one bit, you know set
Well
Anyways, they're really cute, and I wish that I could give what them to you guys, too, you know
Did you hit a birdie or an eagle?
I got my I got every I got under five hits in every fucking hole today. Uh, just about yeah
And you can I have it on panel. I mean on panel. I got it on my YouTube so you can see it
He's not happy with you, dude, he's not happy with you at all
You don't you don't wear those golf clubs when you play you got to wear the gloves on you
Yeah, you got it. It's like a pro glove
There's two kinds there's the one with the fingers that are cut off and the one that goes all the way
Yes, that's kind of disturbing all that reminds me of Adam samar's golfing. Are you on bath salts, bro?
Oh god, please don't be
Wow, he's doing this for you, Paige
No, I don't
That's you, look at the camera
Oh you, right now
You're missing the whole thing
No, we're not doing that
Put your teeth back into your face
No, he actually just said like
He went
Did you just get like your face packed and been here today?
You look so good. You look so good tonight. Look how good they look.
They're all shiny and like...
Where's my glove?
I have a really good toothpaste.
What is it? What is it?
Fucking instant white?
It's called...
What's it called? It's called Marvis.
It's called Marvis. It's on Amazon.
It's really expensive toothpaste.
Marvis. All right. Well, it was like white strips. That's what people use. Yeah, ghost. She's hunting ghosts. Yeah, I like I will go do that if you'd like me to. She's a ghost hunter. Oh yeah. There we go. There we go. Everybody bend over now. I don't know. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I don't know what he said to me, but what I said time for your prostate exam bent over
You must have worked in the morning shit
It's only 10 p.m. It's only 10 17 p.m. Yes early. I think tempered sex. I think that he's having sex tonight
Okay, let's do it. Let's talk on it. Are you gonna do it, too? Yeah, I'll do I have a hard
Okay, well
We don't
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh shit, one, two, three, four, five, oh five seconds, wow.
Why do I get kicked all the time?
I get kicked every time.
Wow, she's a keeper.
Yeah, I'm a fucking winner.
Shit.
She had fucking my ex left, idiot.
You're excellent that sucks
No, no, you can come join join the panel goes we love you didn't know
Thank you, I didn't know that happened. I didn't know that
Go says the more ammo this this month so and summer still has her still or that's over
She used she used we used to her panel. Yeah, we did her panel. We did her her sponsors
Second summer talker is channel. Huh good
Psychi, I didn't know that you know all that had happened and I didn't mean to like I'm off as an asshole
It's okay. You always do, but it's okay. You know, it's like
Thanks. Oh
Wait, I love you. So, you know, I love you. You're not
You're worse than all the one K last night. Oh
All the poor bum you left yesterday not only the poor bum you fucking went overboard
What do you do what do you do? You don't remember what he did. I
Didn't I thought balls balls that like chewing balls. He was fraying on his balls like a twat
Well, yeah, but I deleted it real quickly. I mean, it's I didn't look at it
I just like I just like covered my eyes and screamed
That's disgusting, I mean what I didn't see wasn't happy something like he said he fucking flipped
No, it's just that I put him backstage twice because he was like saying the n-word or like saying like bad things
Yeah
I don't he showed his balls one too many times
The first time he's done
Yeah, three strikes. You're right. This is your important bombs at Edward Bob the ruins the whole show
Please he wasn't even drunk sake he's psyche what I'm saying is did you really ban it? Yes
He pulled off me again, dude. I came from out he won't came in
Forb on me he shouldn't perform on me then it's like that can get my channel deleted you understand and fucks my whole life
My whole life get your channel
Yesterday he tried he got a problem. He if I didn't get a click it off there. I'd be like my channel would be deleted. Yeah, it would be
All right, all right, let's go
No, no, no, I don't want to hear it
You know, it's like I want to ask you about that. Yeah, I was at another
stream last night and
The girl was basically dancing. All right
Mm-hmm. You didn't show any of her titties
Not her she didn't show her ass. She didn't show her fucking pussy nothing
She was just fucking dancing and spreading her legs and rubbing up on her titties with ice and stuff like that
Some okay, some asshole came in the room, right and said oh, this is disgusting
And then two minutes later fucking the whole channel got taken down for sexual content
Yeah, why well, it's a especially okay
Well, it's a part of small channel and it probably was some kind of like, you know
Maybe putting her like ice on the nipple or hard nipples or like stuff like, you know
Nothing was shown but it's still like it's still like, you know
People can get if they're not a they're not an established channel
It's that's why it's especially dangerous when you're just starting a channel because it's like any like little thing
They'll like take down your channel for like I got my channel taken down a couple times
During my beginning phase and it's like because they're more apt to listen to it
But then it's like now I'm going through flagging campaigns and that
The video doesn't even get put on an age-restricted and so you know
They really like to pay attention to like what's actually going on and so
So they took her down for what for dancing
Sexual content like it was too sexual
It was like or and she's this tune too new and it's like and so and then she got maybe mass-flagging or the wrong person
You know though, right? She can appeal and maybe come back. Yeah, but if you monetize if you monetize
She wasn't yeah
It's like not even a big deal. It's like basically that's why also it's because it's not a monetized channel
So they don't really care they'll go to any like little of complaints about a non monetized channel because there's no reason to really
Strike them, then they'll probably take it down. But if it's like, you know
I've been I've been to mass bragging campaigns and that things happen like the worst that's ever happened is sometimes my videos are put on age restricted
You know, and so I'm doing fine on the on YouTube, you know
You get rid of the stream right away, so they don't have nothing to look at so right
Yeah, and that's like it and sometimes it doesn't delete right away
You have to go back a few times and just check for verify because that's that flurry diamonds
Stream our bird ghost and that's a crucible ghost. I don't know why you owe my apology
But I guess he's saying something who's will ghost who's will ghost also
He he basically bought me a computer like a new computer that I'll be able to use for my show
Guys, it's gonna be really exciting because I'll be able to use my microphone
I'll be able to like put stuff on the screen like share some more stuff like I'll be able to do the AI easier
I'll be able to do like
You know just like a lot of cool things with the computer right here instead of just like my tablet
And so thank you. Thank you so much crucible goes for the donations that are going to enable me to buy this new computer and you know
basically
When you give them the panel with what he said pretty much goes unless you know
I'll like fight against it if it's not fair or something like that
But you know, it's like I'm giving him some more time to like, you know
If you want to run the panel if he wants to keep people off and that kind of stuff
He has more credits for that because he did donate a lot like a nice
a nice little money and I really thank you ghosts and so how much more do you need for the computer
No, I think I have enough for the computer. I think I have enough for the computer
I mean, it's like, you know, I'm giving them not buy the most expensive one
They have these new mini computers
I just all I need to do is make sure that it has it will support my my VR headset
And if it can support my VR headset, I can get decent VR and I can do the VR stuff and you know plug in my monitor
plug in my mouse and my keyboard keyboard. That's all I need and
So thank you very much ghost. I love you. No, thank you
Guys, it's like really that it's like send him a handwritten note. Don't don't just tell him and thank you send him a handwritten letter
He'll appreciate. Yeah, I do want to yeah, I do want to you know, thank you more and I will
That's like, you know, I'm gonna give you some I'm gonna give him a lot of value
I don't I don't have his address and it's like onion, you know
So my channel is my channel doesn't matter how many people pay you're gonna give it away sell you is it for sale?
No, it's not for sale. It's not for sale. Here's ghost right here
ghost
Yeah
Stop brother I
Goes how are you?
Good about you
Good I was just the do you know, you know, you still have some some cloud over here
You know and you always will you know, but I want you to feel free if you if you want someone banned for 24 hours
You know you pretty much have free reign. You have some more credits for that and you have some more more sponsored credits
You know, I'm gonna say yeah basically appreciate that man
I was trying to pay attention to the comments, but you're just gonna have to tell me who you want
because your comments get a little crazy sometimes I know well you know people in front of the comments
I don't really want to ban anyone from the chat. I have Ziggy backstage. We're gonna talk to Ziggy here
Talk to Ziggy see if you like Ziggy
Hey earlier
Yeah, what's up?
Yeah, what's up, man? Hey, yummy cat you heard
Oh, oh, she's crazy. She's that was weak. So something's wrong with you. I need it
Which I don't know what it is. There's something wrong with you
We can't do that and there
Psyche, I don't know if you know this but something's wrong with ghosts
What's wrong
I don't know if you know there's something's wrong with the Ziggy as well, you might be terminal. No, I didn't say that
I don't know ghost. Are you sick the only number one up here? It's probably yummy cat. Are you are you sick?
Yeah, no, I don't think he is he doesn't want something he's given his money away like it's nothing
He doesn't have the same energy he usually has
So I mean what would be the argument that would be like cuz I mean what would actually be the argument behind that you just
You just fucking see if it you don't know what the fuck you're talking about excuse my language
You don't fuck you're talking about you got gallbladder issues
What would have anything
Well, I'm asking if I have gallbladder. Let's just let us assume that I do for the sake of argument
Let's say I do have all the issues like I'm just giving my money away
because I
Dying you worried about dying and you're giving your money away. That's why and psych he's my BFF now
Just get him all my money
Okay
Wait wait Gotti man
Gotti, I'm your friend. You know that but
Maybe I don't I don't know this. I don't know him
But he might like
psyche like that
No, I think
That's a fact. I mean say what you're gonna say don't beat around the bush. I mean, but that's not why you sick
Okay, I don't know then I have no idea
You know what? You know what?
That means that means you guys
actually did guess it right.
And that actually is why I'm
giving all my money away.
And no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Yeah, it's me psych. It's me
How are you?
I'm doing great man. I'm doing fucking. Well me and Jay is not doing so good, but you know
everything
You and Jan what the fuck every day it's good
I know I know I know look at the cat look at the cat look at the cat damn cat
Everybody calm down and look at the cat
I need a cat, I want a cat, I want a cat, I want a cat to put in my garage so that it can like eat the mice, that's what I want a cat for.
No, I mean, what, why can't you a cat, I would.
He'd probably burn it.
Yeah, you fucking might yeah, don't do that. Oh, well, I don't know he seems
Sacrifice the cat to Belial
Who's talking that nonsense yummy cat
Actually Ray one it's page you poo and I was actually saying just on what so it's already been talked about before he got up here
My god
Why are you why are you eating? Why are you eating on camera? Why are you eating on camera?
Me I'm eating. I have a salad. I'm hungry. I'm eating my sandwich. It's a baguette. No, I'm talking about yummy cat
So shit. Why are you eating on camera? Are you in tune in for the cat?
He's talking about you me cat
My god, what a slob. Well, what's the matter with you, yummy?
What a slob, why can't he eat dude? What's the matter with that?
I'm pretty good
I don't know
Muck's being on one eighth of my show or one seven
Who cares good you got a woman panel right now. This is like two-thirds of this panel
Yeah
We love we love we love women side. We love
Hey, I will maybe come back, but I got shit. Okay. Bye page. We love you
Here to aid the women. Yeah, okay with the women
Pages leaving because good work guys doesn't like men
Maybe she needs to go hit it into the woods some more
Maybe he needs to go hit it in the woods some more
Maybe she's leaving
She's not a golfer at all. She is not
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Look down here. Don't you have coke zero over there in Malaysia? Where's she live?
No coke zero obviously
That's root. That's root beer. She's drinking coffee. That's root beer. It's clear
Matter of fact, I think a little sense you put her thing down. You can't be doing that
You notice they just pick on the one woman that's left
I don't know. I don't know.
No, it's like psyche. I had you I had psyche you you should let Goddy and these guys pick on yummy
She's the only woman life left
Yummy your name yummy or yummy
It's a yummy
You and me you me
Did did you see I saw her fat husband George York has been coming on here
Did you see George York coming on here?
Who is that?
Her husband
That's her husband. Is that you know, I'd like to take time to apologize for the first time in my life to you
I thought she was big
Or she you know, she's an AI or something. She's not fake her babies. Oh
She's absolutely right. She has
Worship the blood moon I like her lips
Look great. Does she give a little bit to the blood gods? Blood but the blood flow
That's a sign of your judgment body that's real force and simple more brothers
You people know the signs the seven signs. Yeah, that's that's the sign of your judgment
Okay, but is it wrong to judge
No, is it wrong to judge a
It is it is wrong to judge if it's so if you judge you step on God's feet when you judge you step on God's feet. So don't judge but you're not and if you're still a penny or you're stepping on God's feet sir. I will knock you out don't step on my feet. No you're stepping on Jesus' feet.
Okay I put on him sending correct sir.
If I still a penny, I'm stepping on Jesus's feet, sir. What's the Jesus fish?
So so why would you know I'm not still stepping on see sir
So what if you if you kill me you're gonna be in a bad place if you kill me
You're gonna be in a bad place, but you're what if you're already dead. Yeah
I know
Pretty good. Okay. What's uh, what is why are we supposed to talk? What's up?
So Zig Ziggy is dating a Sunday school teacher
That's not bad and
Let him know
Wait wait wait
Look at the lower chest like look at there's a person called I am the and I'm I'm
Look at the picture
What is that why wouldn't you just start why would you even explain all the shit I don't give a fuck you date
And why would you say you're taking a gore porn shit right right exactly who spends that yeah
I mean just fucking go ahead and say it
No, I'm yeah
Explain to me what a Satanist means like what do you do to be a Satanist when I ask that?
Yeah
No, so
He's gonna say that's really interesting
What is actually
Let me ask the question
Ziggy talking a fucking retard
Are you that stupid? You didn't just hear it like the last time fucking?
No, what? What is a Satanism?
What is a Satanism?
Well, thy sin will be judged upon.
Let them talk, and then you just talk over it, but it, go ahead.
Ah, yeah, exactly.
Thank you for shutting that loser down psyche. So what what is the sickness fuck shut me down?
I'm not like you don't fuck. Do I something like
He got the wrong person
Well, you know what a little thing that you know, I'll take it with all three if you guys want it
Let's run that bitch dog
No, so so what what what is the same as T T? Why T why what does this say two of them are fucking losers?
I mean we can have a debate. What do you mean? What what who's the loser?
I think anybody up on here is a fucking movie.
Oh, so you're just already automatically judgmental about anybody.
So it's okay to be judgmental.
I know you don't believe that because you're going to make people to like,
oh, I'm religious, but you know, it's okay to, you can,
you can not judge as a Christian and you should.
No, I'm not, no, no, I'm not religious.
So, so, so aren't you the guy to dump three?
Three or four hundred dollars over the past week. T1. I was not me. That was not me. Yeah, that was. Yeah, you're a ghost. You are a ghost. You're a ghost. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. You're a ghost.
I'm pretty sure I don't feel a little bit more, a little bit ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost, ghost
Oh, because I caught are you talking about what I caught somebody I
Kicked whenever they say something that's so weird
Well, I mean, what's your argument? I mean, I'm talking I guess I'm talking to one person God. What's up?
How you doing kid
I'm not all right yet. Yeah, we're a good one
Pretty good
I was only kidding about you being sick man. I was you know, I was just fucking teasing you now. I'm just fucking with you
I don't know. I don't think it was it. Well, let me talk to this other guy. Thanks. I know that's why it's like you want talking
What was his actual like did he actually want it? There you go. You can talk. Yeah, go ahead. You guys debate about Satanism. Oh
Yeah
No, no straight up like dude, I dude, of course, I believe in God
I mean if you if you have to be a saint in this you
Duh
Believe in God. I just don't like the way the God does things. That's not necessarily though
I don't think that you do you have to I mean
That means that you're taking like the like you're taking everything you're taking like the
Bible scripture and everything
God
No, no, no, no way it goes
the death of my
great aunt
That's your number which is very limited. I know that but go ahead
Fuck that that's stupid dude me and
my friends we're
druggies, and we're fucking allowed to live, come on man, where exactly exactly that's
my that's my argument
Well, so you're trying to make me make an argument for you because like they call you that you're like
Well, why you call me that I can just see that
No, you're taking it wrong what I'm saying is is there's so many that you don't know the fuck you're talking about that's
I'm telling you if you look like a ghost if you listen
There are so many special people in this world that fucking love God
Right, and they fucking go and they go to church and they do everything
you know that and
for me it was never like that and
I was well, there's a lot of people that don't believe them like drugs and shit, but there are also methods out there. I mean
We're gonna use the same logic
I mean, we're gonna have to go all the way
But what you're gonna have to do is you're gonna have to make argument because I'm pretty sure this is what psyche wanted
I think you want us to debate about
I don't know what it was verse like you could verse anything. Yeah, they don't know. They don't know what Satanist doesn't know what the fuck they're talking about there
Well, I do I actually it's better. It's dude. It's the same thing as like I fucking argued and by the way everyone thinks oh you in a
Psyche's best friends. Yeah, we like each other but ask psyche how many times I fucking debate at him on terror readings ask him me
It's been many many
No, no, no, no, no, no. Let me fucking
pull a Jim Brewer on you real quick.
Okay, I do not appreciate anyone,
and that's where that girl, whoever, what, the hair?
When you're worse than them, you realize that, right?
Because you're actually, you're worse than them.
No, no, no, no, no, no, wrong.
No, that's not right.
I don't want to hear you talk. I want you here to bring up an argument and actually talk about it. It's
Hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'all, hey y'
Okay, what actually do you believe in sir go ahead and explain your belief system thought so we're not gonna clap
No, wait wait a second. You just said more to you and you want to why wait T. Why wait to see what do you believe in T. Why
What do you matter that wasn't the debate you fucking retard? I wasn't the debate
What's the argument I asked him?
Obviously he's a sickness. He said he's a sickness. So I asked what he believed in immediately fold it
You're not going to sit here and like, like, question me.
I don't believe in you.
I don't believe in anything.
OK, well, that's fine.
OK, I guess you don't believe me.
No.
And his name, by the way, his name's not T.Y.
It's Ghost.
It's Tony.
You can call me thank you for knowing.
I win. Thank you. You guys you guys really foolish enough to believe. Oh, do you want to feel?
No, how do you win real quick I guarantee I asked you one question. I guarantee you won't answer
Are you battling gotty right now, he's lost already you don't battle my friend, please
Go so you know that he's fake trust me if you made an argument somehow you'd have to like that
It would make sense like you know that Satan is it real that would even make sense pitch
You wouldn't even believe it. They got you you made the you made the debate about Satanism not God
He's not here right now
You know that's all the I run it every single one of you just choose not to listen to the question
Are you just like want to ramble?
We'll ask you again, you know, Satan is fake, right? I
Don't think Satan is sick. Why do you believe in Satan?
It's the light bringer I believe in Satan. I mean, why do you not you but you believe in a fake entity called Satan
But you don't believe I'm God
That makes no sense. Okay. All right. Oh
You see what I'm getting at. Yeah, so what what proof you have of that?
But you're ready to believe a fucking myth over the fact that I'm God right now
Make that make sense. Well, that would be the burden that would be you're playing the burden of proof would be on you
Go ahead
the burden of proof would be on me yes sir you would you like me you not know
I'm supposed to prove to you that a fake being doesn't exist
Ray why you said it did you said it you said it you made the claim the burden of proof would be on you
I'm telling you
That Satan is fake
So God God II God II proved a God isn't real
I don't have to prove that God is a real God is real. You're talking to God right now. You're talking to him right now
Prove that God isn't real Ray. Come on
Ray one than that
Our boy
Now I want to talk to the Satan the same guy
No, but so so prove no if you so prove Satan isn't real God
Proof Satan is a real have to you
You don't have exactly you don't have to don't have to him. He's not real. I
Can talk about math even if I'm on math. I'm not a hypocrite if I say you shouldn't do math. Oh, you do math
Ray say even if I did you know that you know, you shouldn't would I?
Couldn't hear what you said because of these idiots mankind's great. You call an idiot first of all
There would be no such thing as
Are you calling an idiot boy?
When you hey retard, would you like that better bitch? You like that better jit would you like?
Let's run it then. I'm trying to have a religious conversation
And I'm trying to understand you but you sound fucking retarded. You're not gonna talk to me like that
Shut him down. Take him down.
Take him down. Go ahead.
Doesn't mean they were targeted, man.
Here we go.
Yeah, Psyche, you better reckon.
Yeah, let them know.
We're just having a
Psyche, Psyche, this arrogant
motherfucking Narcissus.
We're having a
Just call me a hillbilly.
Take this hill, take this piece of trash down.
I mean, what's wrong with that?
What's the argument?
I'm the argument is that you're argue. No your ghost guy was fucking picking on fucking Ray won
Yeah, I wasn't
I wasn't I
Hear me talk to the Satanist, but everyone else
I really listen to nothing going on right now. Yeah. Yeah, that's what happens. No, let's just talk and be nice
Let's just be friendly. I agree. Good luck with that
Everyone go to Emily by it did by the way go see Emily by attention take your soul by the way, I got
You like that, right? Why do you say that blue just out of blue go to Emily by
The viathan do you know who that is my god the stream and be in this place is off the charts
Then it's in the fucking ocean. I mean my god
It's fucking wicked
Well, me next wife. Hey, it was Emma. She's probably on right now
Go say hi from psyche wiggins, but you can't say my name in her job because it's blocked, but it's right anywhere
My god, come on psych. We're here to see you. We're here. We're here. We're here to see you psych
Huh, we are we're actually here to see you but this ghost guy. He's like, I don't know and don't know
What he's up to
Well, you know what so what's your problem with me because I said something you didn't like I mean
What I said that you didn't like nothing I don't really care
T T why why do you have money? Why do you spend money to have people kicked off, huh?
Yeah, that's kind of weird. We all do it to each other. Maybe you're not a part of the life
I understand that will we do it? Well, I know I never did that. I never did that
Did I pay money to kick you off this pal? He's an animal
Would I pay to kick you off?
Oh
You have no idea what you're talking about. Yeah, we all you're not okay. You're part of the group now
No, I didn't pay to get you kicked off dumb fuck. I feel like you're using your mom
I feel I feel using your I feel I feel so what actually happened though
I feel you are using your mom's money to control these panels
Okay, cool. So I didn't pay to get you kicked off, but you're mad because I had paid to get kicked like summer off
Like even though we always do that shit
She's cool as fuck
He's gay. He is gay. Got gotty. That guy is gay. He's gay
We already know
You just look how he acts. He's a homosexual. I'm not gonna do that cuz you're a man if I if you got kicked off right now
Would I be a misogynist? You're a fucking man. No, it's because
It's always kicked women off
if you kick us, then you're gonna pay him to fucking be like, oh no, who justified it or something.
I'm not gonna kick anyone, can we all just calm down and have a conversation, is that?
I wish, I wish.
Okay, so what, so what do you want to talk about, Mr. Gay?
You can't come back checkmate
he didn't say nothing
oh you're you're you'll never check
you'll never check
oh he just did he checked me
go ahead and try
well well mr. gay
yep
Go ahead because I'm gonna I'm finna crash out on you. Could you say that?
Finna crash
I don't know what that means. I I swear to God. I'm finna crash. Go ahead
Mr. White
Mr. You don't know what the fuck you're talking about mr. You're too fucking stupid
I know what you're talking about. Mr. You're too slow to pronounce your words
To be up here right now
To be up here right so what what the fuck's that your problem, right?
No, that's actually the truth. Yeah, it's not your money
Enjoy some of it. I'll give you some right now. Would you like to enjoy some of it?
No, you know what? Would you like to enjoy some of it? Yes or no sir ghost if I say something
I said no fuck you shut up
Would you like to enjoy some of it right now?
Enjoy what enjoy what some of that money I sent so you're so worried about it
Would you like to enjoy some of it? I seriously doubt that's any of your money
You're spending your mom's money
Okay, would you would you like to enjoy it my last fucking question to speak or chill?
I would you like to enjoy it right now?
$500 does
Okay, yes. Yes, Mr. Mom. I would like to enjoy it.
I mean, I'm not really...
You're this close, bro. I'm done with you, honestly.
You're gonna make an argument you're gonna talk you're gonna be cool. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Mr. Mom. Mr. Mom
I would like to enjoy it mr. Mom be cool or make an argument you're trying to run psyche and it doesn't work
It's not gonna. I'm not trying to run psyche brother. Yeah, you are
Good luck running him
He's crazy
Guys I have a new song from hearing in just a minute. I would give you a little hint about the song one second
So I'm guys don't think I'm going crazy. I might have gone a little bit crazy, but don't think I'm not absolutely crazy
This here song side
You're about to see it. I'm gonna have to put it on by you be a little hint about it. Hold on one second
Hold on oh
I reached my limit. Hold on one second. I just leave this one
One more second
It'll be on a site. Hey site site. I don't have to pay for this like TY does do I?
Making that you keep making other thing you shouldn't you should pay. I mean, well, how's that a bad thing?
How's it that bad thing that I face like?
Well, you know, I might pay him one big one thing I pay make I might pay him one big lump some one day
I could pay him one million dollars. How's that? How's that wrong? Oh my god, you fucking liar. You're such a liar
So you don't know what the fuck you're talking about. So make the argument. How is it bad that I think psyche if you're up here?
Sike get him out. What's song site? I want to hear the song. Let's see who really got a site get him out get him out
Get him out
No, I'm gonna pay him one day. I want to hear the song. Yeah one day, but get him out so I can get him out
So it's you want to get me out get him out
Hello, Psy.
Uh, one second.
Can't hear it.
Without you, I'm stuck in hell.
I was fake Elon, I was Nick Cage too.
Wrote in all caps, I'd steal the moon for you.
Gave you memes, gave you gifts, gave you all my time.
get an old Emma if you can hear me I'm still in the algorithm I still refresh
your channel just to see your face in ten-nail p we could have been
serentock royalty but now now I'm just a ghost in the live stream
your voice, your wit, your stick
I'll light a candle, I'll burn some sage
Still dream of your cards, and you're stuck in this rage
Forever your fool, your cosmic flame
The emerald just whisper my name
Very beautiful
Yeah, I couldn't hear it
I'm sorry guys, but you can't hear it except on the TV, but yeah, I think you guys can hear on the TV. Do you guys like it?
It was weird. I'm sorry
Sorry guys, yeah, I'm sure it was good. I'll play it again later
Who made it in Katrina make it? I made it. Oh, okay
Yeah, she does a really good job making songs
How are you guys? I'll put right back where we're back up. She was sticky left. Hey, everyone
So psych psych that that was amazingly good. That that was you like it
You liked it. Thank you so much. Thank you
Yeah, that's about Emma. I don't know if you I saw Emma Levi's him, but
I miss that loud to you or do you hear it like like half-ass media?
Do what did you hear or do you hear like half-ass audio?
Yeah, I heard it. You you couldn't hear it. What are you paying for man?
What are you paying my question is that you hear alright or just half-ass audio?
No, I heard it and I thought it was a good song
I don't know. I don't. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know.
know. I don't know. I don't know. I
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god
Um, I'm on my phone. That's all the speakers I have, honey.
Okay, got you.
She was Satan's ex, with that fiery stare
Told me my rising sign, like she actually
Without you, I'm stuck in hell
Just getting old, Emma, if you can hear me, I'm still in the algorithm, I still refresh
your channel, just to see your face in 1080p, we could have been Saratuck royalty, but now,
now I'm just a ghost in the livestream for-
You heard that time
Hello
Crucible goes right are you there?
Yeah, you heard that time I heard it
Not in the panel. I heard it. I'm like when I left I heard it pretty good. Is it good? Okay, hopefully they get sir
I heard it like half ass
Okay, I just wanted to play one time
Hopefully she gets she gets it
You know more with that
Kind of summed it up in the words I wanted to sum that up if
Hope she's good though. Hey Emma. I'm a colleague, you know
57 in my chat, you know, not bad. I know you thought I'd be nothing and nobody
but I was and
So there
Thank you for firing me as a boss, so I started my own show and
Now I'm having the time of my life. Thank you
Anyway, so you guys to start my own show
Yeah, well if you want to you know, I want all my mods to be successful. You start your show
Like everyone start a show everyone start doing panels everyone
Let's have like a big big family of it and then we'll be the first ones to really do them
And then we'll be all be famous and rich and we can like fucking do really cool things in the world
That's what I really want. I want us all to be rich and famous all of us
Everybody I come in contact with I want fame and wealth and happiness for
Everybody
Okay
Tty he's sticking it to somebody that blocked him. Why don't you just shut up about it?
Well, I should you
No, I was just testing no, I'm just testing if my mic is still blocked. Okay
Well
Playing the song I'm sorry guys. I'm sorry if I went too far
Psych be honest you keep blocking me when you play the songs
Literally everybody on you what's your argument you put literally everybody on you
Why are you so hurt by that?
Well, he should have said it. We'll discuss it with him. I have that conversation like you say site
You shouldn't put us on block. You shouldn't put us on mute. No, I see I see it
Hey, hey dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb. I see it now. I can I am muted. I
Unmuted I unmuted myself
dummy
You should come with me
No, fuck it. Call me a dummy. Why am I a dummy?
No, I'm saying I see it. I'm saying I
Know I'm not gonna do this you're trying to get you're trying to get a bitch if I want you kicked
I would tell I literally say one
Psyche he's gone. I've never once said that I don't want you cake
He can say it
He can say it though Ray he can say it and I kick you off and you can say it to you pay enough
Enough money. Yeah, I do it to me. You'd be like hey dumb dumb ghost kick. I don't want you cake. I want to have the conversation
Is it okay to have the conversation you're just gonna be a dumb though. I mean, yes, I will whatever
Whatever conversation you want to have, I'll have it. I love the talk.
I agree. Yeah, me too. I love to talk to you, sir.
Alright great. Thank you boss is strong. Oh, thank you. He's giving a member a shout out. Thank you
Yeah, and you guys have been a member for a little month to give a member a shout out
Let me know you've been here like there's like you know, Amanda
I think you could do one just go ahead and say hey, thank you for being a member boss is strong, you know
Awesome. I hope you get that. Have I ever been here for a little month? Are you a member?
Not only for the past week on my new account
Yeah, well if you have to be a member what's your member for a month?
You can do a member milestone like big boss is strong just did you can't do it yet. Yeah
I know I'll give you I'll give you your own if you post a comment
If it was up to me if it was my channel it'd be free but it's not my channel. It's psyche Stanley. You gotta talk to him brother
Not me was psyched psyched this ty gave like five hundred dollars over the past two weeks
Correct
He just
That's why I said he can kick you off in a second. He can be up here. He can like, you know
Be up here psych. He's okay. Okay. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, so
Free speech if it wasn't for a sec, you know, I'm
Free speech absolutists like I don't give a fuck what you say it, but
TOS and it's like yeah, but I
The whole thing is I can take it now know say whatever you want to say to me
I don't want to say anything to you to be honest I mean I'm not I knew that
Yeah, I mean what would I I mean?
I'm kind of like begging for the question now like why would I beg for the argument like why would I be mean?
Yeah, I mean what do the reason?
I mean you're paying a lot of money to take control of this panel my friend so I so sir
If you gave if your friend was struggling
Wanting a laptop and you gave him about like you know like let's just say like $400 whatever
Salt him don't insult him like that. What would the problem? I fuck that. I'm not insulting him
I actually gave money. What would be the problem me give him this money like what's the problem?
I want to hear the argument. What's the problem? Yeah, I did give him money
And he'll admit to you I did, but what's the problem what like I don't understand it
No, there's no if you can afford if you can afford it. There's no problem bitch. I gave the money
I can't afford it. What's the argument? Why are you? I said I said if you can afford it
There's no problem. Okay. Cool. I gave the money. So what's the problem? Shut the fuck up at this point?
There's no
I gave the money here. I gave it
Think I'm not giving it. I gave it
By the way, there's nothing you can fucking do about evening district about it because I already gave it. I think I'm not giving here
So what's the problem?
And now I'm interested what you're talking about now to hold now. I'm interested. Why did you do that? All right?
That's my friend
Why did doc holiday? Well, I can say something you don't understand. Why did doc holiday? He said why dirt?
Because he wanted to have fun that that's my friend, correct
Doc holiday wanted to have fun that day my friend
Psychies my friend. Would you like? Oh my god besides that? Oh my god
Hey, oh D
the
I never had Kentucky gentlemen, but a patient I work with their their husband gave it to me
They're like, what do you like to drink? I'm like twisty scotch bourbon. So you got me Kentucky gentlemen
Would you please shut up I'm how old are you today, Odie? I turned 36 yesterday or two days ago
Happy birthday. It's a great question. Thank you. Oh, it's got that stupid ass on it. I got to get that
Yeah, happy birthday
All right, he's like a no, didn't I kick you off them?
Yeah, you the one that keeps talking and they're gonna keep
You Ray
It's we're gonna be cool from now on. I don't know Ray
Ray
I'm just trying to be nice to everybody. So
Where are you gonna be cool, baby? Yes, I'm gonna be cool
Alright, let me see what this bourbon is like a bourbon
Well, you know, he has to write background color for that bourbon
Pretty smooth honestly, it's pretty smooth for 40%
Ray if you're punching your fucking face like kind of hard
Well, you know, I would duck and come up with a big left hook on you
Let's assume. Have you ever been punching your fucking face really hard?
And so I'm being cool. I'm being cool on here now and you're
Well, you're being cool now, but you weren't being cool. So therefore my question is okay. Have you ever been punching your fucking face?
Ever in your life
No, because I'm too fast. I'm fast. You can't hit me
All right, brother. By the time you cock back, he's already running away
I don't know. I don't know.
You're straight up. You ain't gonna do nothing. You heard
Fucking punk I ain't gonna do nothing over there in it stop fucking fucking like that here straight up
You heard
Gonna crash out on you bitch
No, you don't but you you you using your mom
You don't target me. You using your note. Let me speak. Let me speak you're using your mom's credit card
I'm like a little bitch you sound like a little bitch. You know what the fuck are you talking about?
You could never operate me what you prove in it could never talk to me like we're not on the same skill level
every time
Yeah, you might be feeding you every time I go out at least three more of me. I mean, what are you gonna do?
You're gonna sit there and you're gonna be a good boy. What you're gonna do is shut the fuck up, correct?
So let me talk to my boys like you could you know
Hamlet these boys here
Yeah, who are you ones you got your bag? Well, whoever wants it. I don't want anybody. I'm just trying to choose like
Literally for the first time in my life. I'm I'm literally trying to stay here and show if you have anybody that wants to stay here and show
I'm down
I won't debate. I want to fight, but
Guess what we're gonna do. We're gonna debate and fight. Let's run that rich dog
Well, what do you what do you want a debate about you k-mart motherfucker?
I'm doing time. I thought I was done with you a couple minutes ago, but you want a little piece
Well, you want a little more don't you k-mart you say you want a little piece don't you?
So what the fuck you talking about? What do you mean by k-mart go ahead and explain yourself?
Yeah, well, that's that's a cool pick L. D. What do you mean by Kmart bitch answer Mike?
I like that guy you are talking to me. I'm the motherfucker to ask the question you're
Or you do stupid it really on the motherfucker to ask it
So he could pay he could he could pay all the money and he's gonna abuse your guess
You can pay all the money, you know without you. I'll set down and shut the fuck up
How much money that good?
I
Why would you want to fucking we get this talk? Why would you motherfucking pay to get me kicked off?
We can literally just talk you I literally
Hey boy
Just talk just talk you you pay to get I promise you I really I swear to my mother
shut up I swear to my mother I won't pay to get you kicked off go ahead and say what you gotta say
that was pretty quick
it's not not fair I I literally won't pay say whatever you want I would not pay
I think I think Psycho got rid of them for dropping F-bombs
yeah we're not dropping F-bombs they're not nice I won't I won't do any of that uh so let's start
Was he on here for a while?
Yeah, he was on for a lot argument
Was he was he getting along with people?
No, no, okay. I'll pay for you. Just alright. I'll pay for you. You good?
Yep
For all good. Yeah
Fucking off fucking pay for you then
There's kind of a dick
I don't I don't I don't I don't
I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't
Okay, I'm gonna buy a new new computer or new laptop or something, you know, I'm gonna do something where you can get to be on it and
It'll really improve the show to you. I'll be able to like fucking
Have like a walk put stuff stuff at all kinds of stuff
I'll be able to do I and put my microphone in special microphone in I have a microphone
It's I haven't been able to use it on a show yet. So maybe
Thank you girls. I love you
Restricts
Why is his nose on
Kids in those preps
Was I he's been sniffing
What is that the kitty what they call it shit? This is his regular nose his freckles on us your freckles
Here's a little freckle nose
The pink and dirty nose
People she stopped the message into you the same stop supporting with you. Oh, oh, I'm 71 people on chat
That's the most I've had in tap for a while
Fuck we can't psyche we can't leave a 71. I mean maybe I know we got
But no one's getting a membership. No one's even doing anyone like one dollar
Shit at this point. No one cares. They don't care. They get sick
I'm sorry the one is even supportive can say can see get a little something please. We'll keep it going
You're the only one you're literally the only one that's helping the show and then people are like, oh, yeah
The only person helping the show with it, you know, no, no, I'm sorry. There's I've been with some other people beyond the scenes
But uh, yeah on the show
Publicly, yeah ghost has been
The only person in public can we at least get a $20 donation? That's not it's like yeah, I'm not begging or nothing
I mean that's that's worth keep the show going
No, I don't I don't think it I don't think I
Keep it going 20 bucks. We'll keep it going. Why don't you guys keep doing it?
I
You know what I think like sometimes to get you have to give and so I'll just I'll donate like a membership and like maybe that'll
inspire people to like
Help the show. Let's give a membership away. Fuck it off. I'll try to I give I'll get
Alright, what's up, brother? I didn't see you there. I'll be honest with you
Fuck it. I'll give like 10 bucks anybody else when we get 10 bucks and the chat or on the panel anybody
We all match it. I mean
And bucks I'll give a couple of memberships if you'll give it 10 bucks
Mally you got a membership. Let's give another one
I got you. I got you. I got you.
You got it
Let's let's keep going. Let's keep going
You guys
Go to that. You want to it's a woman doing any membership? I'm don't any some memberships goes to any some memberships
I'm going to donate a couple because I said I would here you go else or I have to anybody else channel
channel
You don't gotta you don't gotta I'm not no I'm doing it. I'm doing it. Here's another one and
BIC you received a membership BIC
Okay, I'm tapped out
but
There you go guys that's the memberships ray one J1 J1
I'm gonna come up in debate with ray one ray one and J1
One yeah, don't bring J1 up here. I bring J1 up
They want to come up. You can come up. Yeah
Amanda thank you for the 99 cents super chat. Hey Brian King
Thank you so much appreciate you Amanda. There's some memberships for the chat traveling gypsy big
And, oh, thank you so much, girls, I appreciate that.
Yeah, guys, I want to have some fun on the show.
I want to, like, you know, also be able to support myself with the show and be able to, like, you know...
Five or five ready to lifeline this shows my life light, you know, it's like and so the show is all good things
Hey, thank you Boston strong
Thank you for you for you and given that give a member shout out because we have over a hundred members on this channel
We have over a hundred members
This is my best month on the show
I really want to thank you guys that
Even behind the scenes been my best month and so thank you guys for everything. I appreciate it
And I I owe you entertainment. I owe you fun entertainment. I don't want to ask you for things
I want to be giving you things. Hey, thank you, Arbiter. Thank you for the $2 super chat
Appreciate it Arbiter that goes. Thank you so much Arbiter
Arbiter of course is an awesome friend. Thank you so much
Yeah, I hope you guys have fun like
And also, you know, I'll have people in this show as long as they're respectful to me
You know, I don't care about what people people are saying about people
I want everybody to come on here and get their side of the story
show decided show decided them another side of the people that might not might not know and
And I believe in forgiveness. I believe in redemption. Okay. So no doubt it's thank. Oh, yeah. Thank you Boston strong
So not to be not to be cheesy or anything, but I really do I believe in I believe that uh, we should forgive people and
People make mistakes right here. We've ghost is back. Thank you so much ghosts for the $2 super chats
Super sticker
Ray you're you're on you're on life
Hey, thanks, what'd you want to say?
Yeah, I just wanted to come up you don't want to apologize
I'd like a little apology. I thought you want to apologize about what apologize about what it'll be
Wasn't that long ago? Come on little apology nothing
Be a Kentucky gentleman
So what kind of cheap shit are you drinking tonight, oh D?
Kentucky gentlemen, what a fucking dumb ass fucking question. No, wouldn't actually enter that you're
I never tried it before it's pretty smooth. I was gifted it
Give me permission to crash off in the crash. Go ahead. Go ahead and crash out, please. Oh crash out
Look, are you just going to take the top off or are you going to break it?
You have absolutely no idea what you're talking about.
If you stupid don't know what you're talking about, you can never be on my level.
You're also too stupid, you're too retarded to have the conversation, you're too stupid to have the conversation, you're too retarded to have the conversation, you're too autistic to have the conversation.
Well listen sir, leave me the fuck alone and shut the fuck up because I'll burn your ass up and you know I will.
I'll burn your ass up
Yeah
You when the way you say sir, I know that you're nor cow you're nor cow T. Why
Don't give a fuck what you're saying bitch leave me the fuck alone off in a crash
Straight up
Texas don't care
You retard it don't the fuck you're talking about
You're too stupid to know what you're talking about.
You're not on my level.
Guys, me and Junkie Jarrett are not on my level.
But you better read some more books, you heard?
Ma, please mute.
Please hide Junkie Jarrett from the channel.
Just hide that person, please.
Thank you so much.
Fucking refaggot.
Let's run that, bitch, dog.
I don't care if you're gonna do it, but you're not gonna be you're gonna talk in this chat. Bye
Please hide
Hi, Amanda. Thank you so much. Hi the person Amanda. Not hide a minute. Hide the person man. Thank you so much
Okay guys
I don't care how much money you don't TY. This isn't your panel. Thank you man
that's psyche's panel and I you know what I'll give another 500 bucks and guess
who's panel it's gonna be it's gonna be psyched
So good
It's psyche's panel. I don't give a fuck how much money I give it's psyche's panel
Hello, hello, are you the same person who's this which we got a witch?
I'm not going to respond to that
Why can't you what are you all what are you gonna respond to?
Jesus Christ
Yeah, oh
Well, you're scaring Ld when you say that
I'm trying to say he's like he explained but he's being weird. I mean
I mean the only person you should fear is Jesus Christ himself
It where are you from?
Does the matter where she's from your she said what she said you're it does matter
She sounds young it
So I'm psych psych is she 18 is she?
31 years old she's 31
Gonna be a year. That's how your guy gets down here
All four and then
I'll tell you, LD, if you roll your eyes up one more time, boy.
Man, bitch, what? I'm telling you right now, bitch. Let's rock and run it.
Are you stupid to do it? Let's fucking run that bitch.
No, he keeps rolling his eyes up like he's smarter than everybody else.
A big ghost is here now. I'm telling you what I'm doing.
What the fuck do you mean? Let's run that bitch.
Why are you fucking nice?
Well, fuck all that shit. Let's run that bitch, though.
Why can't you guys be nice?
Ah, we men.
Shut the fuck up.
I mean, there's nothing wrong with this.
Be quiet.
Be quiet, we're men.
Shut the fuck up.
Well now, now, everybody loves Duke.
Everybody loves Duke.
What's wrong with this?
Are you okay, sweetie?
Nah, babe, that bitch's better.
Get the men running.
Sike, are you sure this person is old enough to be on here?
Yes, he's 31 years old, he's 31 years old.
No reason to lie. Okay. I was born in 94. Ain't nobody gonna check me. You heard good. Check me. Go ahead. Check me
Go ahead and check me
Yeah, you go ahead and hold on don't be a whole wrong
Only person that you should fear Joseph what Joseph what?
What's wrong that bitch?
Nothing in this world
So so you're gonna come up here trying to preach the Bible. So hey, hey
So what's your name? What's your name little girl? What's your name?
Rc you are speak the Bible what you don't know the Bible says
Rc Rc you're gonna come up here and try to preach the Bible to us. Are you serious something in the chat?
I'm not trying to preach anything somebody asked me something in chat
Who said what in chat?
You might you might be a fucking whore
You can be whatever you want within this within this within your life
No, if T why would shut up we could let this little 17 year old
This little 17 year old girl talk
Yeah, you're being weird, bro. Why is this something you're fucking creep? Oh, yeah, you would like
Yeah, you would like it wouldn't you you fucking weirdo
What the fuck up? I'm trying to teach
Yeah
Why am I trying to meet up with 13 year old you fucking little piece of shit. I think what if you're in my fucking city
I punch the vibe not you the fuck out yours
Straight up. Where do you where do you live at T? Why? Where do you look out straight up?
I'd punch you. Hey, where do you where do you live at boy? Where do you live at?
Yeah, boy, if you lived over here boy, you catch a slug you heard you know what a slug is
You'd catch. Yeah. Yeah. I thought you I thought you wouldn't say it or rapist you little dumbass
Whenever you like that you little weirdo
Straight up I'd burn your little fucking foggy ass up you heard
You know, I put it on for them. What are you gonna do? You're gonna set them. You're gonna shut the fuck up, aren't you?
LD LD LD so you don't have any new girls
You all you want. Ah, well shut up and let me speak. You don't have
Should I do it
No, this stupid motherfucker won't shut up
What do you want to talk about no you're gone
You are very disrespectful by the way
Well, you're done, too
Bye, dumb fuck
Don't
This stupid evening talk
What's up, man? How you doing?
So watch anything chillin out. What are you doing, man?
Just watching some shit on TV laying around my dog drinking some beers and whiskey. I gotta get other beer actually
I'm watching the fucking noon. I'm having trouble with it
You're watching the blood
I'm having trouble. I'm watching the new
I'm watching an old TV show
Wow, it's like it's called banshee
Yeah, but aren't they all like bad asses on that or something?
And maybe we can talk later, man. I yeah
Here's a drinking
Don't you in a bit tonight? What are you drinking?
Budweiser, what are you drinking?
Yingling from the East Coast
I'm far far East Coast
Finest beer in America
Yeah, I get about 30 seconds before what
No, they're all going to come at me, brother.
I don't even, I don't even really pay attention to checks. I'm pretty sure someone banned me in it, so
I'm like, why, why respond to people that can't even see me?
Sure, Scott's pretty good speech.
Yeah, man, you got any pets or anything you got any, you know, you got cats like psych or something.
I said, do you have any pets like cats, dogs?